<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<library>
	<book id="1" title="The Lusty Argonian Maid I">
		<p>
			The Lusty Argonian Maid, Part I<br />
			Crassius Curio
		</p>
		<p>
			Act IV, Scene III, continued
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: Certainly not, kind sir! I am here but to clean your chambers.
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Is that all you have come here for, little one? My chambers?
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: I have no idea what it is you imply, master. I am but a poor Argonian maid.
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: So you are, my dumpling. And a good one at that. Such strong legs and shapely tail.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: You embarrass me, sir!
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Fear not. You are safe here with me.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: I must finish my cleaning, sir. The mistress will have my head if I do not!
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Cleaning, eh? I have something for you. Here. Polish my spear.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: But it is huge! It could take me all night!
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Plenty of time, my sweet. Plenty of time.
		</p>
		<p>
			END OF ACT IV, SCENE III
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="2" title="The Lusty Argonian Maid II">
		<p>
			The Lusty Argonian Maid, Part II<br />
			Crassius Curio
		</p>
		<p>
			Act VII, Scene II, Continued
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: My goodness, that's quite a loaf! But how ever shall it fit my oven?
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: This loaf isn't ready for baking, my sweet. It has yet to rise.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: If only we could hurry that along. How would I accomplish such a task?
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Oh, my foolish little Argonian maid, you must use your hands.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: You wish me to knead the loaf? Here?
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Of course.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: But what if the mistress catches me? Your loaf was meant to satisfy her appetite.
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Don't fret, my delicate flower. I'll satisfy the mistress' cravings later.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifts-Her-Tail: Very well, but I'm afraid my oven isn't hot enough. It could take hours!
		</p>
		<p>
			Crantius Colto: Plenty of time, my sweet. Plenty of time.
		</p>
		<p>
			END OF ACT VII, SCENE II
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="3" title="Bestiary I">
		<p>
			<b>Succubus</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			In medieval legend, a succubus (plural succubi; from Latin succuba; "prostitute") is a demon which takes the form of a female to seduce men (especially monks) in dreams to have sexual intercourse. They draw energy from the men to sustain themselves, often until the point of exhaustion or death of the victim. From mythology and fantasy, Lilith and the Lilin (Jewish), Lilitu (Sumerian) and Rusalka (Slavic) are, in redactive Christian fables (folktales not part of official Christian theology), considered succubi.
		</p>
		<p>
			According to the Malleus Maleficarum, or "Witches' Hammer", succubi would collect semen from the men they slept with, which incubi would then use to impregnate women. Children so begotten were supposed to be more susceptible to the influence of demons.
		</p>
		<p>
			In some beliefs the succubi would morph into the Incubus with its newly collected semen ready to impregnate their victims. This was to account for the fact that demons could not reproduce naturally, however the incubus could impregnate women.
		</p>
		<p>
			From the 16th century, the carving of a succubus on the outside of an inn indicated that the establishment also operated as a brothel. In a similar fashion, modern marketing has found that embedding photos of smiling people in web sites and other advertisements subconsciously makes viewers want to purchase products and services.
		</p>
		<p>
			The appearance of succubi varies just about as much as that of demons in general; there is no single definitive depiction. However, they are almost universally depicted as alluring women with unearthly beauty, often with demonic batlike wings; occasionally, they will be given other demonic features (horns, a tail with a spaded tip, snakelike eyes, hooves, etc). Occasionally they appear simply as an attractive woman in dreams that the victim cannot seem to get off their mind. They lure males and in some cases, the male has seemed to fall "in love" with her. Even out of the dream she will not leave his mind. She will remain there slowly draining energy from him.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="4" title="Brief History of the Empire I">
		<p>
			A Brief History of the Empire<br />
			Part One
		</p>
		<p>
			Stronach k'Thojj III
			Imperial Historian
		</p>
		<p>
			Before the rule of Tiber Septim, all Tamriel was in chaos.  The poet Tracizis called that period of continuous unrest "days and nights of blood and venom."  The kings were a petty lot of grasping tyrants, who fought Tiber's attempts to bring order to the land.  But they were as disorganized as they were dissolute, and the strong hand of Septim brought peace forcibly to Tamriel.  The year was 2E 896.  The following year, the Emperor declared the beginning of a new Era-thus began the Third Era, Year Aught.
		</p>
		<p>
			For thirty-eight years, the Emperor Tiber reigned supreme.  It was a lawful, pious, and glorious age, when justice was known to one and all, from serf to sovereign.  On Tiber's death, it rained for an entire fortnight as if the land of Tamriel itself was weeping.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Emperor's grandson, Pelagius, came to the throne.  Though his reign was short, he was as strong and resolute as his father had been, and Tamriel could have enjoyed a continuation of the Golden Age.  Alas, an unknown enemy of the Septim Family hired that accursed organization of cutthroats, the Dark Brotherhood, to kill the Emperor Pelagius I as he knelt at prayer at the Temple of the One in the Imperial City.  Pelagius I's reign lasted less than three years.
		</p>
		<p>
			Pelagius had no living children, so the Crown Imperial passed to his first cousin, the daughter of Tiber's brother Agnorith.  Kintyra, former Queen of Silvenar, assumed the throne as Kintyra I.  Her reign was blessed with prosperity and good harvests, and she herself was an avid patroness of art, music, and dance.
		</p>
		<p>
			Kintyra's son was crowned after her death, the first Emperor of Tamriel to use the imperial name Uriel.  Uriel I was the great lawmaker of the Septim Dynasty, and a promoter of independent organizations and guilds.  Under his kind but firm hand, the Fighters Guild and the Mages Guild increased in prominence throughout Tamriel.  His son and successor Uriel II reigned for eighteen years, from the death of Uriel I in 3E64 to Pelagius II's accession in 3E82.  Tragically, the rule of Uriel II was cursed with blights, plagues, and insurrections.  The tenderness he inherited from his father did not serve Tamriel well, and little justice was done.
		</p>
		<p>
			Pelagius II inherited not only the throne from his father, but the debt from the latter's poor financial and judicial management.  Pelagius dismissed all of the Elder Council, and allowed only those willing to pay great sums to resume their seats.  He encouraged similar acts among his vassals, the kings of Tamriel, and by the end of his seventeen year reign, Tamriel had returned to prosperity.  His critics, however, have suggested that any advisor possessed of wisdom but not of gold had been summarily ousted by Pelagius.  This may have led to some of the troubles his son Antiochus faced when he in turn became Emperor.
		</p>
		<p>
			Antiochus was certainly one of the more flamboyant members of the usually austere Septim Family.  He had numerous mistresses and nearly as many wives, and was renowned for the grandeur of his dress and his high good humor.  Unfortunately, his reign was rife with civil war, surpassing even that of his grandfather Uriel II.  The War of the Isle in 3E110, twelve years after Antiochus assumed the throne, nearly took the province of Summurset Isle away from Tamriel.  The united alliance of the kings of Summurset and Antiochus only managed to defeat King Orghum of the island-kingdom of Pyandonea due to a freak storm.  Legend credits the Psijic Order of the Isle of Artaeum with the sorcery behind the tempest.
		</p>
		<p>
			The story of Kintyra II, heiress to her father Antiochus' throne, is certainly one of the saddest tales in imperial history.  Her first cousin Uriel, son of Queen Potema of Solitude, accused Kintyra of being a bastard, alluding to the infamous decadence of the Imperial City during her father's reign.  When this accusation failed to stop her coronation, Uriel bought the support of several disgruntled kings of High Rock, Skyrim, and Morrowind, and with Queen Potema's assistance, he coordinated three attacks on the Septim Empire.
		</p>
		<p>
			The first attack occurred in the Iliac Bay region, which separates High Rock and Hammerfell.  Kintyra's entourage was massacred and the Empress taken captive.  For two years, Kintyra II languished in an Imperial prison believed to be somewhere in Glenpoint or Glenmoril before she was slain in her cell under mysterious circumstances.  The second attack was on a series of Imperial garrisons along the coastal Morrowind islands.  The Empress' consort Kontin Arynx fell defending the forts.  The third and final attack was a siege of the Imperial City itself, occurring after the Elder Council had split up the army to attack western High Rock and eastern Morrowind.  The weakened government had little defence against Uriel's determined aggression, and capitulated after only a fortnight of resistance.  Uriel took the throne that same evening and proclaimed himself Uriel III, Emperor of Tamriel.  The year was 3E 121.  Thus began the War of the Red Diamond, described in Volume II of this series.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="5" title="Brief History of the Empire II">
		<p>
			A Brief History of the Empire<br />
			Part Two
		</p>
		<p>
			Stronach k'Thojj III
			Imperial Historian
		</p>
		<p>
			Volume I of this series described in brief the lives of the first eight Emperors of the Septim Dynasty, beginning with the glorious Tiber Septim and ending with his great, great, great, great, grandniece Kintyra II.  Kintyra's murder in Glenpoint while in captivity is considered by some to be the end of the pure strain of Septim blood in the imperial family.  Certainly it marks the end of something significant.
		</p>
		<p>
			Uriel III not only proclaimed himself Emperor of Tamriel, but also Uriel Septim III, taking the eminent surname as a title.  In truth, his surname was Mantiarco from his father's line.  In time, Uriel III was deposed and his crimes reviled, but the tradition of taking the name Septim as a title for the Emperor of Tamriel did not die with him.
		</p>
		<p>
			For six years, the War of the Red Diamond (which takes its name from the Septim Family's famous badge) tore the Empire apart.  The combatants were the three surviving children of Pelagius II-Potema, Cephorus, and Magnus-and their various offspring.  Potema, of course, supported her son Uriel III, and had the combined support of all of Skyrim and northern Morrowind.  With the efforts of Cephorus and Magnus, however, the province of High Rock turned coat.  The provinces of Hammerfell, Summurset Isle, Valenwood, Elsweyr, and Black Marsh were divided in their loyalty, but most kings supported Cephorus and Magnus.
		</p>
		<p>
			In 3E127, Uriel III was captured at the Battle of Ichidag in Hammerfell.  En route to his trial in the Imperial City, a mob overtook his prisoner's carriage and burned him alive within it.  His captor and uncle continued on to the Imperial City, and by common acclaim was proclaimed Cephorus I, Emperor of Tamriel.
		</p>
		<p>
			Cephorus' reign was marked by nothing but war.  By all accounts, he was a kind and intelligent man, but what Tamriel needed was a great warrior -- and he, fortunately, was that.  It took an additional ten years of constant warfare for him to defeat his sister Potema.  The so-called Wolf Queen of Solitude who died in the siege of her city-state in the year 137.  Cephorus survived his sister by only three years.  He never had time during the war years to marry, so it was his brother, the fourth child of Pelagius II, who assumed the throne.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Emperor Magnus was already elderly when he took up the imperial diadem, and the business of punishing the traitorous kings of the War of the Red Diamond drained much of his remaining strength.  Legend accuses Magnus' son and heir Pelagius III of patricide, but that seems highly unlikely-for no other reason than that Pelagius was King of Solitude following the death of Potema, and seldom visited the Imperial City.
		</p>
		<p>
			Pelagius III, sometimes called Pelagius the Mad, was proclaimed Emperor in the 145th year of the Third Era.  Almost from the start, his eccentricities of behaviour were noted at court.  He embarrassed dignitaries, offended his vassal kings, and on one occasion marked the end of an imperial grand ball by attempting to hang himself.  His long-suffering wife was finally awarded the Regency of Tamriel, and Pelagius III was sent to a series of healing institutions and asylums until his death in 3E153 at the age of thirty-four.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Empress Regent of Tamriel was proclaimed Empress Katariah I upon the death of her husband.  Some who do not mark the end of the Septim bloodline with the death of Kintyra II consider the ascendancy of this Dark Elf woman the true mark of its decline.  Her defenders, on the other hand, assert that though Katariah was not descended from Tiber, the son she had with Pelagius was, so the imperial chain did continue.  Despite racist assertions to the contrary, Katariah's forty-six-year reign was one of the most celebrated in Tamriel's history.  Uncomfortable in the Imperial City, Katariah travelled extensively throughout the Empire such as no Emperor ever had since Tiber's day.  She repaired much of the damage that previous emperor's broken alliances and bungled diplomacy created.  The people of Tamriel came to love their Empress far more than the nobility did.  Katariah's death in a minor skirmish in Black Marsh is a favorite subject of conspiracy minded historians.  The Sage Montalius' discovery, for instance, of a disenfranchised branch of the Septim Family and their involvement with the skirmish was a revelation indeed.
		</p>
		<p>
			When Cassynder assumed the throne upon the death of his mother, he was already middle-aged.  Only half Elven, he aged like a Breton.  In fact, he had left the rule of Wayrest to his half-brother Uriel due to poor health.  Nevertheless, as the only true blood relation of Pelagius and thus Tiber, he was pressed into accepting the throne.  To no one's surprise, the Emperor Cassynder's reign did not last long.  In two years he joined his predecessors in eternal slumber.
		</p>
		<p>
			Uriel Lariat, Cassynder's half-brother, and the child of Katariah I and her Imperial consort Gallivere Lariat (after the death of Pelagius III), left the kingdom of Wayrest to reign as Uriel IV.  Legally, Uriel IV was a Septim:  Cassynder had adopted him into the royal family when he had become King of Wayrest.  Nevertheless, to the Council and the people of Tamriel, he was a bastard child of Katariah.  Uriel did not possess the dynamism of his mother, and his long forty-three-year reign was a hotbed of sedition.
		</p>
		<p>
			Uriel IV's story is told in the third volume of this series.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="6" title="Brief History of the Empire III">
		<p>
			A Brief History of the Empire<br />
			Part Three
		</p>
		<p>
			by
			Stronach k'Thojj III
			Imperial Historian
		</p>
		<p>
			The first volume of this series told in brief the story of the succession of the first eight Emperors of the Septim Dynasty, from Tiber I to Kintyra II.  The second volume described the War of the Red Diamond and the six Emperors that followed its aftermath, from Uriel III to Cassynder I.  At the end of that volume, it was described how the Emperor Cassynder's half-brother Uriel IV assumed the throne of the Empire of Tamriel.
		</p>
		<p>
			It will be recalled that Uriel IV was not a Septim by birth.  His mother, though she reigned as Empress for many years, was a Dark Elf married to a true Septim Emperor, Pelagius III.  Uriel's father was actually Katariah I's consort after Pelagius' death, a Breton nobleman named Gallivere Lariat.  Before taking the throne of Empire, Cassynder I had ruled the kingdom of Wayrest, but poor health had forced him to retire.  Cassynder had no children, so he legally adopted his half-brother Uriel and abdicated the kingdom.  Seven years later, Cassynder inherited the Empire at the death of his mother.  Three years after that, Uriel once again found himself the recipient of Cassynder's inheritance.
		</p>
		<p>
			Uriel IV's reign was a long and difficult one.  Despite being a legally adopted member of the Septim Family, and despite the Lariat Family's high position -- indeed, they were distant cousins of the Septims -- few of the Elder Council could be persuaded to accept him fully as a blood descendant of Tiber.  The Council had assumed much responsibility during Katariah I's long reign and Cassynder I's short one, and a strong-willed "alien" monarch like Uriel IV found it impossible to command their unswerving fealty.  Time and again the Council and Emperor were at odds, and time and again the Council won the battles.  Since the days of Pelagius II, the Elder Council had consisted of the wealthiest men and women in the Empire, and the power they wielded was conclusive.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Council's last victory over Uriel IV was posthumous.  Andorak, Uriel IV's son, was disinherited by vote of Council, and a cousin more closely related to the original Septim line was proclaimed Cephorus II in 3E247.  For the first nine years of Cephorus II's reign, those loyal to Andorak battled the Imperial forces.  In an act that the Sage Eraintine called "Tiber Septim's heart beating no more," the Council granted Andorak the High Rock kingdom of Shornhelm to end the war, and Andorak's descendants still rule there.
		</p>
		<p>
			By and large, Cephorus II had foes that demanded more of his attention than Andorak.  "From out of a cimmerian nightmare," in the words of Eraintine, a man who called himself the Camoran Usurper led an army of Daedra and undead warriors on a rampage through Valenwood, conquering kingdom after kingdom.  Few could resist his onslaughts, and as month turned to bloody month in the year 3E249, even fewer tried.  Cephorus II sent more and more mercenaries into Hammerfell to stop the Usurper's northward march, but they were bribed or slaughtered and raised as undead.
		</p>
		<p>
			The story of the Camoran Usurper deserves a book of its own.  (It is recommended that the reader find Palaux Illthre's The Fall of the Usurper for more detail.)  In short, however, the destruction of the forces of the Usurper had little do with the efforts of the Emperor.  The result was a great regional victory and an increase in hostility toward the seemingly inefficacious Empire.
		</p>
		<p>
			Uriel V, Cephorus II's son and successor, swivelled opinion back toward the latent power of the Empire.  Turning the attention of Tamriel away from internal strife, Uriel V embarked on a series of invasions beginning almost from the moment he took the throne in 3E268.  Uriel V conquered Roscrea in 271, Cathnoquey in 276, Yneslea in 279, and Esroniet in 284.  In 3E288, he embarked on his most ambitious enterprise, the invasion of the continent kingdom of Akavir.  This ultimately proved a failure, for two years later Uriel V was killed in Akavir on the battlefield of Ionith.  Nevertheless, Uriel V holds a reputation second only to Tiber as one of the two great Warrior Emperors of Tamriel.
		</p>
		<p>
			The last four Emperors, beginning with Uriel V's infant son, are described in the fourth and final volume of this series.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="7" title="Brief History of the Empire IV">
		<p>
			A Brief History of the Empire<br />
			Part Four
		</p>
		<p>
			Stronach k'Thojj III<br />
			Imperial Historian
		</p>
		<p>
			The first book of this series described, in brief, the first eight Emperors of the Septim Dynasty beginning with Tiber I.  The second volume described the War of the Red Diamond and the six Emperors who followed.  The third volume described the troubles of the next three Emperors-the frustrated Uriel IV, the ineffectual Cephorus II, and the heroic Uriel V.
		</p>
		<p>
			On Uriel V's death across the sea in distant, hostile Akavir, Uriel VI was but five years old.  In fact, Uriel VI was born only shortly before his father left for Akavir.  Uriel V's only other progeny, by a morganatic alliance, were the twins Morihatha and Eloisa, who had been born a month after Uriel V left.  Uriel VI was crowned in the 290th year of the Third Era.  The Imperial Consort Thonica, as the boy's mother, was given a restricted Regency until Uriel VI reached his majority.  The Elder Council retained the real power, as they had ever since the days of Katariah I.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Council so enjoyed its unlimited and unrestricted freedom to promulgate laws (and generate profits) that Uriel VI was not given full license to rule until 307, when he was already 22 years old.  He had been slowly assuming positions of responsibility for years, but both the Council and his mother, who enjoyed even her limited Regency, were loath to hand over the reins.  By the time he came to the throne, the mechanisms of government gave him little power except for that of the imperial veto.
		</p>
		<p>
			This power, however, he regularly and vigorously exercised.  By 313, Uriel VI could boast with conviction that he truly did rule Tamriel.  He utilized defunct spy networks and guard units to bully and coerce the difficult members of the Elder Council.  His half-sister Morihatha was (not surprisingly) his staunchest ally, especially after her marriage to Baron Ulfe Gersen of Winterhold brought her considerable wealth and influence.  As the Sage Ugaridge said, "Uriel V conquered Esroniet, but Uriel VI conquered the Elder Council."
		</p>
		<p>
			When Uriel VI fell off a horse and could not be resuscitated by the finest Imperial healers, his beloved sister Morihatha took up the imperial tiara.  At 25 years of age, she had been described by (admittedly self-serving) diplomats as the most beautiful creature in all of Tamriel.  She was certainly well-learned, vivacious, athletic, and a well-practised politician.  She brought the Archmagister of Skyrim to the Imperial City and created the second Imperial Battlemage since the days of Tiber Septim.
		</p>
		<p>
			Morihatha finished the job her brother had begun, and made the Imperial Province a true government under the Empress (and later, the Emperor).  Outside the Imperial Province, however, the Empire had been slowly disintegrating.  Open revolutions and civil wars had raged unchallenged since the days of her grandfather Cephorus II.  Carefully coordinating her counterattacks, Morihatha slowly claimed back her rebellious vassals, always avoiding overextending herself.
		</p>
		<p>
			Though Morihatha's military campaigns were remarkably successful, her deliberate pace often frustrated the Council.  One Councilman, an Argonian who took the Colovian name of Thoricles Romus, furious at her refusal to send troops to his troubled Black Marsh, is commonly believed to have hired the assassins who claimed her life in 3E 339.  Romus was summarily tried and executed, though he protested his innocence to the last.
		</p>
		<p>
			Morihatha had no surviving children, and Eloisa had died of a fever four years before.  Eloisa's 25-year-old son Pelagius was thus crowned Pelagius IV.  Pelagius IV continued his aunt's work, slowly bringing back under his wing the radical and refractory kingdoms, duchies, and baronies of the Empire.  He exercised Morihatha's poise and circumspect pace in his endeavours-but alas, he did not attain her success.  The kingdoms had been free of constraint for so long that even a benign Imperial presence was considered odious.  Nevertheless, when Pelagius died after a notably stable and prosperous twenty-nine-year reign, Tamriel was closer to unity than it had been since the days of Uriel I.
		</p>
		<p>
			Our current Emperor, His Awesome and Terrible Majesty, Uriel Septim VII, son of Pelagius IV, has the diligence of his great-aunt Morihatha, the political skill of his great-uncle Uriel VI, and the military prowess of his great grand-uncle Uriel V.  For twenty-one years he reigned and brought justice and order to Tamriel.  In the year 3E389, however, his Imperial Battlemage, Jagar Tharn, betrayed him.
		</p>
		<p>
			Uriel VII was imprisoned in a dimension of Tharn's creation, and Tharn used his sorcery of illusion to assume the Emperor's aspect.  For the next ten years, Tharn abused imperial privilege but did not continue Uriel VII's schedule of reconquest.  It is not yet entirely known what Tharn's goals and personal accomplishments were during the ten years he masqueraded as his liege lord.  In 3E399, an enigmatic Champion defeated the Battlemage in the dungeons of the Imperial Palace and freed Uriel VII from his other-dimensional jail.
		</p>
		<p>
			Since his emancipation, Uriel Septim VII has worked diligently to renew the battles that would reunite Tamriel.  Tharn's interference broke the momentum, it is true -- but the years since then have proven that there is hope of the Golden Age of Tiber Septim's rule glorifying Tamriel once again.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="8" title="Short History of Morrowind">
		<p>
			A Short History of Morrowind
		</p>
		<p>
			Jeanette Sitte
		</p>
		<p>
			[from the Introduction]
		</p>
		<p>
			Led by the legendary prophet Veloth, the ancestors of the Dunmer, exiles from Altmer cultures in present-day Summerset Isle, came to the region of Morrowind. In earliest times the Dunmer were harassed or dominated by Nord sea raiders. When the scattered Dunmer tribes consolidated into the predecessors of the modern Great House clans, they threw out the Nord oppressors and successfully resisted further incursions.
		</p>
		<p>
			The ancient ancestor worship of the tribes was in time superseded by the monolithic Tribunal Temple theocracy, and the Dunmer grew into a great nation called Resdayn. Resdayn was the last of the provinces to submit to Tiber Septim; like Black Marsh, it was never successfully invaded, and was peacefully incorporated by treaty into the Empire as the Province of Morrowind.
		</p>
		<p>
			Almost four centuries after the coming of the Imperial Legions, Morrowind is still occupied by Imperial legions, with a figurehead Imperial King, though the Empire has reserved most functions of the traditional local government to the Ruling Councils of the Five Great Houses....
		</p>
		<p>
			[on Vvardenfell District]
		</p>
		<p>
			In 3E 414, Vvardenfell Territory, previously a Temple preserve under Imperial protection, was reorganized as an Imperial Provincial District. Vvardenfell had been maintained as a preserve administrated by the Temple since the Treaty of the Armistice, and except for a few Great House settlements sanctioned by the Temple, Vvardenfell was previously uninhabited and undeveloped. But when the centuries-old Temple ban on trade and settlement of Vvardenfell was revoked by King of Morrowind, a flood of Imperial colonists and Great House Dunmer came to Vvardenfell, expanding old settlements and building new ones.
		</p>
		<p>
			The new District was divided into Redoran, Hlaalu, Telvanni, and Temple Districts, each separately administered by local House Councils or Temple Priesthoods, and all under the advice and consent of Duke Dren and the District Council in Ebonheart. Local law became a mixture of House Law and Imperial Law in House Districts, jointly enforced by House guards and Legion guards, with Temple law and Imperial law enforced in the Temple district by Ordinators. The Temple was still recognized as the majority religion, but worship of the Nine Divines was protected by the legions and encouraged by Imperial cult missions.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Temple District included the city of Vivec, the fortress of Ghostgate, and all sacred and profane sites (including those Blighted areas inside the Ghostfence) and all unsettled and wilderness areas on Vvardenfell. In practice, this district included all parts of Vvardenfell not claimed for Redoran, Hlaalu, or Telvanni Districts. The Temple stubbornly fought all development in their district, and were largely successful.
		</p>
		<p>
			House Hlaalu in combination with Imperial colonists embarked on a vigorous campaign of settlement and development. In the decades after reorganization, Balmora and the Ascadian Isles regions have grown steadily. Caldera and Pelagiad are completely new settlements, and all legion forts were expanded to accommodate larger garrisons.
		</p>
		<p>
			House Telvanni, normally conservative and isolationist, has been surprisingly aggressive in expanding beyond their traditional tower villages. Disregarding the protests of the other Houses, the Temple, the Duke, and the District council, Telvanni pioneers have been encroaching on the wild lands reserved to the Temple. The Telvanni council officially disavows responsibility for these rogue Telvanni settlements, but it is an open secret that they are encouraged and supported by ambitious Telvanni mage-lords.
		</p>
		<p>
			Under pressure from the Temple, conservative House Redoran has steadfastly resisted expansion in their district. As a result, House Redoran and the Temple are in danger of being politically and economically marginalized by the more aggressive and expansionist Hlaalu and Telvanni interests.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Imperial administration faces many challenges in the Vvardenfell district, but the most serious are the Great House rivalries, animosity from the Ashlander nomads, internal conflicts within the Temple itself, and the Red Mountain blight. Struggles between Great House, Temple, and Imperial interests to control Vvardenfell's resource could at any time erupt into full-scale war. Ashlanders raid settlements, plunder caravans, and kill foreigners on their wild lands. The Temple has unsuccessfully attempted to silence criticism and calls for reform within its ranks.
		</p>
		<p>
			But most serious are the plagues and diseased hosts produced by the blight storms sweeping out from Red Mountain. Vvardenfell and all Morrowind have long been menaced by the legendary evils of Dagoth Ur and his ash vampire kin dwelling beneath Red Mountain. For centuries the Temple has contained this threat within the Ghostfence. But recently the Temple's resources and will have faltered, and the threat from Red Mountain has grown in scale and intensity. If the Ghostfence should fail, and hosts of blighted monsters were to spill out across Vvardenfell's towns and villages, the Empire might have no choice but to evacuate Vvardenfell district and abandon it to disease and corruption.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="9" title="Book of the Dragonborn">
		<p>
			The Book of the Dragonborn
		</p>
		<p>
			Prior Emelene Madrine<br />
			Order of Talos<br />
			Weynon Priory
		</p>
		<p>
			Year 360 of the Third Era,<br />
			Twenty-First of the Reign of His Majesty Pelagius IV
		</p>
		<p>
			Many people have heard the term "Dragonborn" - we are of course ruled by the "Dragonborn Emperors" - but the true meaning of the term is not commonly understood. For those of us in the Order of Talos, this is a subject near and dear to our hearts, and in this book I will attempt to illuminate the history and significance of those known as Dragonborn down through the ages.
		</p>
		<p>
			Most scholars agree that the term was first used in connection with the Covenant of Akatosh, when the blessed St. Alessia was given the Amulet of Kings and the Dragonfires in the Temple of the One were first lit. "Akatosh, looking with pity upon the plight of men, drew precious blood from his own heart, and blessed St. Alessia with this blood of Dragons, and made a Covenant that so long as Alessia's generations were true to the dragon blood, Akatosh would endeavor to seal tight the Gates of Oblivion, and to deny the armies of daedra and undead to their enemies, the Daedra-loving Ayleids." Those blessed by Akatosh with "the dragon blood" became known more simply as Dragonborn.
		</p>
		<p>
			The connection with the rulers of the Empire was thus there from the beginning - only those of the dragon blood were able to wear the Amulet of Kings and light the Dragonfires. All the legitimate rulers of the Empire have been Dragonborn - the Emperors and Empresses of the first Cyrodilic Empire founded by Alessia; Reman Cyrodiil and his heirs; and of course Tiber Septim and his heirs, down to our current Emperor, His Majesty Pelagius Septim IV.
		</p>
		<p>
			Because of this connection with the Emperors, however, the other significance of the Dragonborn has been obscured and largely forgotten by all but scholars and those of us dedicated to the service of the blessed Talos, Who Was Tiber Septim. Very few realize that being Dragonborn is not a simple matter of heredity - being the blessing of Akatosh Himself, it is beyond our understanding exactly how and why it is bestowed. Those who become Emperor and light the Dragonfires are surely Dragonborn - the proof is in the wearing of the Amulet and the lighting of the Fires. But were they Dragonborn and thus able to do these things - or was the doing the sign of the blessing of Akatosh descending upon them? All that we can say is that it is both, and neither - a divine mystery.
		</p>
		<p>
			The line of Septims have all been Dragonborn, of course, which is one reason the simplistic notion of it being hereditary has become so commonplace. But we know for certain that the early Cyrodilic rulers were not all related. There is also no evidence that Reman Cyrodiil was descended from Alessia, although there are many legends that would make it so, most of them dating from the time of Reman and likely attempts to legitimize his rule. We know that the Blades, usually thought of as the Emperor's bodyguards, originated in Akaviri crusaders who invaded Tamriel for obscure reasons in the late First Era. They appear to have been searching for a Dragonborn - the events at Pale Pass bear this out - and the Akaviri were the first to proclaim Reman Cyrodiil as Dragonborn. In fact it was the Akaviri who did the most to promote his standing as Emperor (although Reman himself never took that title in his lifetime). And of course there is no known hereditary connection between Tiber Septim and any of the previous Dragonborn rulers of Tamriel.
		</p>
		<p>
			Whether there can be more than one Dragonborn at any time is another mystery. The Emperors have done their best to dismiss this notion, but of course the Imperial succession itself means that at the very least there are two or more potential Dragonborn at any time: the current ruler and his or her heirs. The history of the Blades also hints at this - although little is known of their activities during the Interregnum between Reman's Empire and the rise of Tiber Septim, many believe that the Blades continued to search out and guard those they believed were (or might be) Dragonborn during this time.
		</p>
		<p>
			Lastly, we come to the question of the true meaning of being Dragonborn. The connection with dragons is so obvious that it has almost been forgotten - in these days when dragons are a distant memory, we forget that in the early days being Dragonborn meant having "the dragon blood". Some scholars believe that was meant quite literally, although the exact significance is not known. The Nords tell tales of Dragonborn heroes who were great dragonslayers, able to steal the power of the dragons they killed. Indeed, it is well known that the Akaviri sought out and killed many dragons during their invasion, and there is some evidence that this continued after they became Reman Cyrodiil's Dragonguard (again, the connection to dragons) - the direct predecessor to the Blades of today.
		</p>
		<p>
			I leave you with what is known as "The Prophecy of the Dragonborn". It often said to originate in an Elder Scroll, although it is sometimes also attributed to the ancient Akaviri. Many have attempted to decipher it, and many have also believed that its omens had been fulfilled and that the advent of the "Last Dragonborn" was at hand. I make no claims as an interpreter of prophecy, but it does suggest that the true significance of Akatosh's gift to mortalkind has yet to be fully understood.
		</p>
		<p>
			When misrule takes its place at the eight corners of the world<br />
			When the Brass Tower walks and Time is reshaped<br />
			When the thrice-blessed fail and the Red Tower trembles<br />
			When the Dragonborn Ruler loses his throne, and the White Tower falls<br />
			When the Snow Tower lies sundered, kingless, bleeding<br />
			The World-Eater wakes, and the Wheel turns upon the Last Dragonborn.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="10" title="The Bear of Markarth">
		[pagebreak]
		<p>
			The Bear of Markarth<br />
			The Crimes of Ulfric Stormcloak
		</p>
		<p>
			Arrianus Arius<br />
			Imperial Scholar
		</p>
		<p>
			Ulfric Stormcloak is considered a hero by many for his part in quelling the Forsworn Uprising. It is said that when the Empire abandoned Skyrim, and the natives of the Reach rebelled (undoubtedly due to the Nords poor treatment of them), Ulfric Stormcloak and his militia was there to retake "their" land from the Forsworn. In all the bravado and epic yarns the skalds compose of his exploits, you would think Ulfric to be a giant of a man, equal to that of Tiber Septim in his cunning, leadership, and decisive actions.
		</p>
		<p>
			But the truth is far more revealing. Yes, from 4E 174-176, the Forsworn did in fact rule over the Reach as an independent kingdom from Skyrim. Yes, this was accomplished while the Empire was beset by Aldmeri Dominion forces and could not send the Legion to re-establish order. And yes, Ulfric Stormcloak did quell the rebellion without Imperial assistance. That much is true, but what the bards often fail to tell in their stories is that the Forsworn Kingdom was quite peaceful for those 2 years they were in power.
		</p>
		<p>
			True, some crimes were committed against former Nord landowners (often those accused of being the harshest towards their native workers), but on the whole the Forsworn ruled their lands fairly, and were making overtures to be recognized by the Empire as a legitimate kingdom.
		</p>
		<p>
			In the wake of the aftermath of the Great War, you can imagine the backlog on stately matters the Empire had. Before a peace treaty could be resolved with the Forsworn, a militia led by Ulfric Stormcloak sieged the gates of their capital, Markarth. What happened during that battle was war, but what happened after the battle was over is nothing short of war crimes.
		</p>
		<p>
			Every official who worked for the Forsworn was put to the sword, even after they had surrendered. Native women were tortured to give up names of Forsworn fighters who had fled the city or were in the hills of the Reach. Anyone who lived in the city, Forsworn and Nord alike, were executed if they had not fought with Ulfric and his men when they breached the gates. "You are with us, or you are against Skyrim" was the message on Ulfric's lips as he ordered the deaths of shopkeepers, farmers, the elderly, and any child old enough to lift a sword that  had failed in the call to fight with him.
		</p>
		<p>
			So when a "grateful" Empire accepted Ulfric's victory and sent soldiers to re-establish the rule of law in the Reach, it was no surprise that he would demand to be allowed to worship Talos freely before the Legion could enter. With chaos running through the streets of Markarth and the reports of deaths rising every day, the Empire had no choice but to grant Ulfric and his men their worship.
		</p>
		<p>
			We allowed them to worship Talos, in full violation of the White-Gold Concordat with the Aldmeri Dominion (which recognizes the elven belief that Talos, as a human, cannot be one of the Divines). In jeopardizing the treaty that so many sacrificed for during the Great War, the Empire was wrong. But what choice did they have, I ask you? Against the Bear of Markarth, Ulfric Stormcloak, "no" is not an answer.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="11" title="Chaurus Pie">
		<p>
			Chaurus Pie:<br />
			A Recipe
		</p>
		<p>
			If I have to hear one more time about that famous gourmet who wrote that recipe book, I'll hack off my own ears with a blunt axe.
		</p>
		<p>
			Sure, he can cook up some dishes fit for them stodgy Imperials and them poncy Bretons, but real Nords want real Nord food, and my chaurus pie is just that.
		</p>
		<p>
			I guess I been complaining a lot about it, cause Susanna was yelling at me. Nils, she says, if your chaurus pie is so good, you should write down the recipe.
		</p>
		<p>
			Well, I ain't good with my letters and I got no talent for writing, but I thought why not give it a go? So this here's my first ever recipe that I wrote down and I hope you like it.
		</p>
		<p>
			First thing you'll need is some chaurus meat and that ain't easy to come by. Chauruses mostly live in caves, and as like as not they share them caves with other nasty things.
		</p>
		<p>
			If you go hunting for chaurus meat to make some dinner with, make sure you don't end up as dinner yourself. Haha.
		</p>
		<p>
			Anyway, like I was saying, get yourself some good armor and a nice big sword, and if you've got some stout men who won't run off at the first sign of trouble - in other words, not like one of them poncy Bretons - then go looking in caves and you'll find a chaurus sooner or later.
		</p>
		<p>
			They look like big bugs the size of really big dogs, and mind you watch out for that acid they spit. That'll ruin your armor pretty quick.
		</p>
		<p>
			Now once you got some chaurus meat, you got to put it on a spit. Make sure you get that white, thick meat from the midsection. Don't use that yellow meat from the head or legs, because that's got poisonous acid in it and if you eat it, you'll probably die.
		</p>
		<p>
			So you cook up your chaurus on the spit. And you want to baste it with sauce. To make that, grind up some tomatoes into pulp and then mix that with water, peppers, honey and salt. And then you have to boil it all together.
		</p>
		<p>
			I wouldn't use too many peppers, but you want a few spoons of salt. How much honey you use is up to you. Depends on how sweet you want it.
		</p>
		<p>
			When the chaurus is done and you've basted it enough, then you want to bake it in a pie with some potatoes, carrots and apples. And put the rest of that sauce you made in there, too.
		</p>
		<p>
			If you want turnips, sometimes those are good. Depends on what you're in the mood for.
		</p>
		<p>
			Then you cook that for awhile. Look for the top to be light brown, that's when you know it's done.
		</p>
		<p>
			And that's it. Easy as pie. Haha.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="12" title="On Oblivion">
		<p>
			On Oblivion
		</p>
		<p>
			Morian Zenas
		</p>
		<p>
			It is improper, however customary, to refer to the denizens of the dimension of Oblivion as "demons."  This practice probably dates to the Alessian Doctrines of the First Era prophet Marukh -- which, rather amusingly, forbade "trafficke with daimons" and then neglected to explain what daimons were.
		</p>
		<p>
			It is most probable that "daimon" is a misspelling or etymological rendition of "Daedra," the old Elven word for those strange, powerful creatures of uncertain motivation who hail from the dimension of Oblivion.  ("Daedra" is actually the plural form; the singular is "Daedroth.")  In a later tract by King Hale the Pious of Skyrim, almost a thousand years after the publication of the original Doctrines, the evil machinations of his political enemies are compared to "the wickedness of the demons of Oblivion... their depravity equals that of Sanguine itself, they are cruel as Boethiah, calculating as Molag Bal, and mad as Sheogorath."  Hale the Pious thus long-windedly introduced four of the Daedra lords to written record.
		</p>
		<p>
			But the written record is not, after all, the best way to research Oblivion and the Daedra who inhabit it.  Those who "trafficke with daimons" seldom wish it to be a matter of public account.  Nevertheless, scattered throughout the literature of the First Era are diaries, journals, notices for witch burnings, and guides for Daedra-slayers.  These I have used as my primary source material.  They are at least as trustworthy as the Daedra lords I have actually summoned and spoken with at length.
		</p>
		<p>
			Apparently, Oblivion is a place composed of many lands -- thus the many names for which Oblivion is synonymous:  Coldharbour, Quagmire, Moonshadow, etc.  It may be correctly supposed that each land of Oblivion is ruled over by one prince.  The Daedra princes whose names appear over and over in ancient records (though this is not an infallible test of their authenticity or explicit existence, to be sure) are the afore-mentioned Sanguine, Boethiah, Molag Bal, and Sheogorath, and in addition, Azura, Mephala, Clavicus Vile, Vaernima, Malacath, Hoermius (or Hermaeus or Hormaius or Herma -- there seems to be no one accepted spelling) Mora, Namira, Jyggalag, Nocturnal, Mehrunes Dagon, and Peryite.
		</p>
		<p>
			From my experience, Daedra are a very mixed lot.  It is almost impossible to categorize them as a whole except for their immense power and penchant for extremism.  Be that as it may, I have here attempted to do so in a few cases, purely for the sake of scholastic expediency.
		</p>
		<p>
			Mehrunes Dagon, Molag Bal, Peryite, Boethiah, and Vaernima are among the most consistently "demonic" of the Daedra, in the sense that their spheres seem to be destructive in nature.  The other Daedra can, of course, be equally dangerous, but seldom purely for the sake of destruction as these five can.  Nor are these previous five identical in their destructiveness.  Mehrunes Dagon seems to prefer natural disasters -- earthquakes and volcanoes -- for venting his anger.  Molag Bal elects the employment of other daedra, and Boethiah inspires the arms of mortal warriors.  Peryite's sphere seems to be pestilence, and Vaernima's torture.
		</p>
		<p>
			In preparation for the next instalment in this series, I will be investigating two matters that have intrigued me since I began my career as a Daedra researcher.  The first is on one particular Daedroth, perhaps yet another Daedra prince, referred to in multiple articles of incunabula as Hircine.  Hircine has been called "the Huntsman of the Princes" and "the Father of Man-beasts," but I have yet to find anyone who can summon him.  The other, and perhaps more doubtful, goal I have is to find a practical means for mortal men to pass through to Oblivion.  It has always been my philosophy that we need only fear that which we do not understand -- and with that thought in mind, I ever pursue my objective.
		</p>
	</book>
	<book id="13" title="Wraith's Wedding Dowry">
		<p>
			The Wraith's Wedding Dowry
		</p>
		<p>
			Voltha gra-Yamwort<br />
			(translated by Apthorne)
		</p>
		<p>
			"The poets are right.  There is something life-changing about being in love," said Kepkajna gra-Minfang, sometimes called the Wraith. "I haven't wanted to rob anyone or anything in weeks.  Why, the other day, I saw the door wide open at a wealthy merchant's house, but my mind was fully occupied with what I should wear on my wedding day."
		</p>
		<p>
			"You have been out of the right society for very long now," frowned her friend Khargol approvingly. "You never told me what happened to your first husband, you know, the one the shaman gave you?"
		</p>
		<p>
			"Torn apart by ash ghouls," smiled Kepkajna dreamily. "It was rather saddish.  But I know nothing like that would happen to Wodworg.  No life of adventure for him.  He's practically an Imperial.  In fact, he is one.  Did I tell you how we met?"
		</p>
		<p>
			"Hundreds of times," grumbled Khargol, reaching for his flagon. "He was your jailer, and he refused you food until you promised to marry him."
		</p>
		<p>
			"Have you ever heard of anything so madly romantic in all your life?" sighed Kepkajna, and then grew serious. "I was going to say that I hope my old friends will wish me well, but as Old Bosriel used to say, there's no point in hoping for what cannot be.  We'll leave with the Imperial Knights for Balmora immediately after the wedding, but as long as we're in Dagon Fel, the gang will find some way of disrupting my love life and bring me back to the light.  I know it."
		</p>
		<p>
			As the days approached towards the Wraith's wedding day, there was certainly something sinister in the air that Kepkajna could smell when she was not transported by heady bliss.  Dark figures seemed to shift in the shadows and disappear when approached.  She recognized the clothing of some beggars near Wodworg's cottage as costumes, but the mendicants hurried away before she could recognize which of her old gang was stalking her.
		</p>
		<p>
			But these moments of apprehension were few.  Kepkajna was truly happy, making arrangements for the ceremony to be performed at the very dungeon where Wodworg had imprisoned her.  Her father was long since dead -- another victim of the ash ghouls -- but her fiance's commander volunteered to act in his behalf.  Of course, Kepkajna had to supply her own dowry.  She spent every last mark of her savings of ill-gotten gain to buy her beloved a truly wonderful present.
		</p>
		<p>
			The wedding was set for the stroke of midnight, as is Orc tradition.  The handmaidens, wives of Imperial officers, were busily sewing her into her gown of red velvet and fine gold filigree in the mid-morning.  Dolcetta, one of the handmaidens, remarked that she had heard that Kepkajna had bought Wodworg a truly beautiful gift for her dowry.
		</p>
		<p>
			"Let me show it to you," Kepkajna giggled, dashing from the room half-dressed to her hidden alcove.  The present had been stolen.
		</p>
		<p>
			The women were horrified, but the Wraith found herself merely irritated, not surprised.  This was truly the old gang's style.  They knew that a wedding ceremony without a dowry was marked as unlucky.  She asked her handmaidens to finish dressing her quickly while she pondered what the burglars would have done with her treasure.
		</p>
		<p>
			The whole region was honeycombed with secret lairs and abandoned sites thieves used to store their loot.  There were obvious places, of course, but after much reflection, she thought of where she would have put it under similar circumstances.  Once the handmaids had finished, Kepkajna bade them to make certain that the ceremony went on as scheduled, and not to fret as she might be a little late.  She wrapped herself in a shawl to protect her gown from dungeon dust and set off for the Shrine of Malacath.
		</p>
		<p>
			The Wraith had never before attempted to rob her own friends, and though she was peeved at them for trying to ruin her happiness, she had no interest in hurting them physically.  Her style was to avoid conflict, though she knew it would be inevitable.  The lessons her mentor Khargol had given her had helped her avoid the lances and blades of guards and Imperial Knights over the years: now she would see if they would allow her to survive a den of thieves and the unknown dangers of the Shrine.  Without, most importantly, ruining her dress.
		</p>
		<p>
			The desolate place was so empty as she delved into it that she feared she might have made a miscalculation.  It was not until she found the small room hidden down a long corridor that she knew she was at the right place, and that it was well suited for an ambush.  She grabbed the chest with her treasure within, and turned to face the assault.
		</p>
		<p>
			Two of her old gang, Yorum and Yohr-i the Redguard twin brother and sister, were outside the door as she came from the room.  They knew the Wraith better than to taunt her and immediately attacked.  Yorum struck out with a left thrust of his blade while Yohr-i sought to rush her.  The Wraith neatly sidestepped Yohr-i, while dropping her weight to her rear left leg, shifting her right shoulder to the left to slip past Yorum's strike.  The twins crashed into one another and Kepkajna passed swiftly on.
		</p>
		<p>
			Almost immediately, she was set on by the Argonian Binyaar, his mace whistling through the air at her head.  They had never much liked one another.  The Wraith snapped into a duck, so the mace whacked with a tremendous clamor against the stone wall.  Binyaar was thrown off balance, giving her a few seconds lead hurrying up the passage.  Ahead she could smell the fresh night air.
		</p>
		<p>
			The last of her dowry's defenders was Sorogth, an Orc with whom she had shared a brief romance.  It was he who Kepkajna knew had masterminded the theft.  In a way and in context, she thought, his devotion to her misery was rather sweet.  At the moment, though, she was most concerned with avoiding his barbed ax that seemed ideal for breaking her dress's fine stitchwork and the flesh beneath.
		</p>
		<p>
			Bending her knees slightly, bobbing to avoid strikes to the head, weaving her head to confuse Sorogth of her next move, shuffling her feet arrhythmically, the Wraith made an impossible target.  She ducked inside his thrusts, sidestepped his swings, and then sidestepped his thrusts, and ducked his swings.  As erratic as she tried to make her defensive moves, Sorogth still kept pace with her, refusing to budge from his position at the dungeon outlet.
		</p>
		<p>
			Midnight was coming, and the Wraith finally decided that she must end the confrontation.  When Sorogth swung out next, she sidestepped to her left, swayed down, and ducked her head, so the ax whistled over her right shoulder.  In that instant, his right side was exposed, and she reluctantly smashed the chest hard into his torso.  There was not enough time for Kepkajna to see if she had killed him or merely knocked him unconscious.  In truth, she thought of nothing else but rushing to her wedding ceremony.
		</p>
		<p>
			At precisely midnight, Wodworg and Kepkajna were united together.  He was delighted with her dowry gift, a fine suit of armor that would make him the envy of other Imperial jailers.  Even more, he was enchanted by his wife's tale of retrieving it from the Shrine of Malacath.
		</p>
		<p>
			"Did it occur to you to put on the armor when you knew that it was an ambush?" he asked.
		</p>
		<p>
			"I didn't want to dent your present," she replied, between kisses. "And I certainly didn't want to wrinkle my gown."
		</p>
	</book>
</library>
