<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE scenes [
	<!ELEMENT scenes (scene+)>
	<!ELEMENT scene (filter*,(p|script)*,action*)>
	<!ELEMENT filter EMPTY>
	<!ELEMENT p (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT script (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT action EMPTY>
	<!ATTLIST scene
		id CDATA #REQUIRED
		name CDATA #REQUIRED
		list CDATA #IMPLIED
	>
	<!ATTLIST filter
		target (top|bottom) #REQUIRED
		type CDATA #REQUIRED
		name CDATA #IMPLIED
		value CDATA #IMPLIED
	>
	<!ATTLIST script language CDATA #FIXED "text/noxicobotic">
	<!ATTLIST action name CDATA #REQUIRED>
]>
<scenes>
	<scene id="TamaniStartBoy" name="(starting node)">
		<!-- This is a comment that'll show up in the editor. -->
		<filter target="bottom" type="name" name="Emi Nakashima" />
		<p>
			Tamani is here, grinning wolfishly.
		</p>
		<script language="text/noxicobotic">
			<![CDATA[
				$top.checktag "penis"
				if exists
					|<<	"Ready for another fuck, big boy?" >>
				else
					|<<	"Ready for another fuck, big girl?" >>
				endif
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="tamani take her" />
		<action name="tamani let her" />
		<action name="tamani decline" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="TamaniTakeHer" name="tamani take her" list="Take her">
		<filter target="bottom" type="name" name="Emi Nakashima" />
		<script language="text/noxicobotic">
			<![CDATA[
				$top.getcockcount
				cox = it
				$top.getcumamount
				cum = it

				$top.getcockarea
				if it > 90
					|<<	You grab hold of the insensate goblin by her pink-dyed hair and shove her into the mud,
							irritated with her constant demands and rape attempts. The horny slut doesn't even have
							the grace to be ashamed of her defeat. She just lies in the mud, wiggling her exposed
							ass back and forth in the air, trying to tempt you with it.
							[break]
							It's too tempting of a target to resist. You allow your [t:multicockdescript] to flop
							free. You're already hard from the enticing display, and in a moment you're pressing
							against her lust-slicked >>
					if cox > 1
						|<<	pussy and tight asshole. >>
					else
						|<<	pussy. >>
					endif
					|<<	You don't allow her any say in the matter, pushing forward as you feel the small girl's
							flesh yield around >>
					if cox > 1
						|<<	each of your girths. >>
					else
						|<<	your girth. >>
					endif
					|<<	She squeals happily, clearly getting what she desires. For a moment you feel disappointed
							in yourself, but the sensations of her tight >>
					if cox > 1
						|<<	holes >>
					else
						|<<		hole >>
					endif
					|<<	clenching and squeezing around you quickly washes it away.
							[break] >>

				else

					|<<	You throw Tamani on her back, too drunk on desire to care how it feels for the tiny slut.
							There's no way she could ever take >>
					if cox > 1
						|<<	any of your massive members, >>
					else
						|<<	your massive member, >>
					|<<	so you grab her by the ankles and wrap her soft-soled feet about yourself. You start
							jerking yourself off, using Tamani as a cute but expendable masturbation aid. She chews
							a fingernail and massages her [b:breastdescript] as she watches you, doing her best to
							put on a show. The little slut seems to like it.
							[break]
							Her feet start to grow slick with your sweat and precum, sliding effortlessly along the
							length of your shaft as you continue to bring yourself towards orgasm. You watch while
							Tamani dips her fingers into the slick folds of her hungry cunt, getting off on being
							used in such a perverse manner. She coos, "How do my feet feel stud? Are they soft and
							slick when they slide on your cock? Are you going to cum for Tamani and paint her white?
							You are. You know you are. Cum for Tamani."
							[break] >>

				endif
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="tamani take her 2" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="TamaniTakeHer2" name="tamani take her 2" list="">
		<script language="text/noxicobotic">
			<![CDATA[
				$top.getcockcount
				cox = it
				$top.getcumamount
				cum = it

				$top.getcockarea
				if it <= 90
					|<<	You rock back and forth methodically, treating Tamani like a tight cock-sleeve.
							The goblin slut's hands rub her belly, not even attempting to pull her face out of the
							mud as she moans and giggles like a whore. You keep working her cunt like a [t:gender]
							possessed, sawing in and out with brutal efficiency, the wet squelches of the slut's
							juices driving you to piston back and forth with even greater force. She gurgles happily, >>
					if cox > 1
						|<<	her holes squeezing tightly as she cums hard.[break] >>
					else
						|<<	her pussy squeezing tightly as she cums hard.[break] >>

					if cox > 1
						|<<	Each of your [t:multicockdescript] pulsates, >>
					else
						|<<	Your [t:multicockdescript] pulsates, >>
					endif
					|<<	spasming inside your goblin-flesh prison, spraying a bit of sticky goo into the happy
							slut. You can hear her babbling, pleasure-drunk as she quivers around you, "Fuck yes!
							Cu-ah-ahm in me! Fuck fuckfuckfucKFUCKYEAH! Oooh that's it put me in the dirt and show
							me who's boss!" >>

				else

					|<<	Oh gods you do... it'd be so easy to just release all over her tight little body, soaking
							her in cum from head to toe. You know she'd like it. Hell, you'd like it, but you want to
							make her wait. Your hands keep sliding and squeezing, jerking her now-slippery soles with
							faster and faster strokes. Holding back is TOO hard! You need to release – the little slut's
							words ring true as you squeeze tightly, feeling warmth building in your crotch as your body
							begins to climax.
							[break]
							Tamani licks her lips and pushes with her legs, assisting you as you milk yourself with her
							feet, squeezing out the first jet of hot goblin-treat. It spatters over the green girl's
							forehead, running into her pink highlights. She opens wide, craning up to catch the next
							blast of salty seed in her dirty lipstick-coated mouth. Swallowing like a pro, she leans up
							further, letting you coat her tits with cream.
							[break] >>

				endif
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="tamani take her 3" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="TamaniTakeHer3" name="tamani take her 3" list="">
		<script language="text/noxicobotic">
			<![CDATA[
				$top.getcockcount
				cox = it
				$top.getcumamount
				cum = it

				$top.getcockarea
				if it <= 90
					|<< The words seem to have the desired effect, helping you empty every
							ounce of cock-cream into the slut's tight >>
					if cox > 1
						|<<	holes. >>
					else
						|<<	hole. >>
					endif
					if cum >= 250
						|<<	She pants, turning her head in the mud to watch as her belly visibly inflates,
								stuffed totally full of cum. >>
					endif
					if cum >= 500
						|<<	In no time at all a river of jism pours from her, pooling below as you overwhelm her
								body's capacity to store spunk. >>
					endif

					|<<	[break]Tamani winks, sucking on her finger as she staggers up. She coos, "Mmmm Tamani
							loves it when her stud dominates her. Do you think your >>
					$top.checktag "balls"
					if exists
						|<<	sexy balls have >>
					else
						|<<	sweet cock has >>
					endif
					|<<	any more cream to give to me?"
							[break]
							She doesn't give you a chance to answer as she wobbles off, jiggling pleasantly in all
							the right places. "Of course you do. I'll be back for the rest later!" >>

					$top.settagval "climax" 0
					$bottom.settagval "climax" 0

				else

					if cum >= 250
						|<<	You continue working your [t:cockdescript] with her supple feet, watching your dripping
								spooge froth and bubble as you continue to pump more onto the sassy wench. >>
					endif
					if cum >= 500
						|<<	She sputters, blowing some of the caked up semen off her face so she can breathe. The
								slut gathers up the goopy mess as you continue to paint her, alternatively devouring it
								with her mouth and shoveling drippy handfuls into her eager cunt. >>
					endif

					|<<	[break]Tamani winks, blinking the cum out of an eye as you finish up, releasing her
							seed-covered form. She coos, "Mmmm Tamani loves it when you dominate her, stud. Do you
							think your >>
					$top.checktag "balls"
					if exists
						|<<	sexy balls have >>
					else
						|<<	sweet cock has >>
					endif
					|<<	any more cream to give to me?"
							[break]
							She doesn't give you a chance to answer as she staggers up and strikes a sexy pose.
							"Of course you do. I'll be back for the rest later!"
							[break]
							Tamani wiggles in the sexiest way as she leaves, arousing your body all over again... >>

					$top.settagval "climax" 35
					$bottom.settagval "climax" 0

				endif
			]]>
		</script>
	</scene>

	<scene id="TamaniDecline" name="tamani decline" list="&quot;No.&quot;">
		<filter target="bottom" type="npc" value="Tamani" />
		<p>
			Tamani adopts a fighting pose and says, "If I have to I'll beat my
			children out of you!"
		</p>
		<script language="text/noxicobotic">
			<![CDATA[
				$bottom.addtag "hostile"
				<<< Tamani has gone hostile!
			]]>
		</script>
	</scene>

	<scene id="EmiTest" name="(starting node)">
		<filter target="bottom" type="name" name="Emi Nakashima" />
		<p>
			Your [t:cockdescript] stirs as [b:name] looks deep in your &lt;c[t:T:eyes/color]>[t:t:eyes/color]&lt;c> eyes.
		</p>
	</scene>
	<scene id="MulticockTest1" name="(starting node)">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" value="1" />
		<p>
			Exactly one cock.
		</p>
	</scene>
	<scene id="MulticockTest2" name="(starting node)">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" value="2" />
		<p>
			Exactly two cocks.
		</p>
	</scene>
	<scene id="MulticockTest3" name="(starting node)">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" value="2+" />
		<p>
			Two or more cocks.
		</p>
	</scene>
	<scene id="DevStart" name="(starting node)">
		<filter target="bottom" type="gender" value="male" />
		<p>
			Development starting node, male bottom.
		</p>
		<p>
			Second paragraph.
		</p>
		<short>[t:name] triggers devstart.</short>
		<action name="dev action 1" />
		<action name="dev leave" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="DevStart2" name="(starting node)">
		<filter target="bottom" type="gender" value="female" />
		<p>
			Development starting node, female bottom.
		</p>
		<p>
			Second paragraph.
		</p>
		<short>[t:name] triggers devstart.</short>
		<action name="dev action 1" />
		<action name="dev leave" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="DevAction1" name="dev action 1" list="Do a jig">
		<p>
			Testing scripts...
		</p>
		<script language="text/noxicobotic">
			<![CDATA[
  			|<< Second paragraph from script. >>
  		]]>
		</script>
		<action name="dev climax" />
		<action name="dev leave" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="DevClimax" name="dev climax" list="Test climax">
		<script language="text/noxicobotic">
			<![CDATA[
  			|<< Increasing climax for top by 20. >>
				$top.inctagval "Climax" 20
  		]]>
		</script>
		<action name="dev climax" />
		<action name="dev leave" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="DevLeave" name="dev leave" list="Leave">
		<p>Baibai</p>
	</scene>

	<scene id="FinalDestination" name="(starting node)">
		<p>If you can see this, all the other nodes failed.</p>
	</scene>
</scenes>