<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE scenes [
	<!ELEMENT scenes (scene+)>
	<!ELEMENT scene (filter*,(p|script)*,action*)>
	<!ELEMENT filter EMPTY>
	<!ELEMENT p (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT script (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT action EMPTY>
	<!ATTLIST scene
		id CDATA #REQUIRED
		name CDATA #REQUIRED
		list CDATA #IMPLIED
		priority CDATA #IMPLIED
	>
	<!ATTLIST filter
		target (top|bottom) #REQUIRED
		type CDATA #REQUIRED
		name CDATA #IMPLIED
		value CDATA #IMPLIED
	>
	<!ATTLIST script type CDATA #FIXED "text/javascript">
	<!ATTLIST action name CDATA #REQUIRED>
]>
<scenes>
	<!-- Chelsie the Cheetah, by Bodshivita -->

	<!-- For when caught in the introduction phase -->
	<scene id="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmit" name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmit" list="Submit">
		<p>
			You nod slowly in acceptance and ask what offering would be acceptable. The ferocious huntress smiles again, this time with mirth, as she turns and dashes away. She turns right back at you, picking up momentum before leaping towards you. You wonder for a moment what she's doing.
		</p>
		<p>
			Your shock-widened eyes catch a glance at her inflamed lower lips. Your field of vision is quickly filled by the sight of her cunt as the plush pussy lips slam down upon your face and knock you to the ground. Now mounted and thoroughly aroused by the aerial face plant, you groan against her snatch, your lips pressed against her drenched twat as intimately as any woman's lips as she roughly grinds her hips against your face.
		</p>
		<p>
			She bucks her body up, down, and back again as she rides your femspunk covered face. "Daaamn, ooo~oh! Lick my pussy like a kitten who wants a li'l milk, you useless [b:g:bitch:bastard:nobody]~!" 
		</p>
		<action name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitCheck" />
	</scene>

	<scene id="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA" name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitCheck" list="==>">
		<filter target="bottom" type="skill" name="cunnilingus" value="0" />
		<p>
			Thrashing your [b:tongue] out blindly, you attempt to please the crazy cat bitch using your face as if it were some kind of toy. The mysterious huntress winces and hits you on the head as your crap-ass efforts come to nothing.
		</p>
		<p>
			"What the hell is wrong with you?! What? You've never gone out to eat or something?! What are ya, gynophobic?! Don't like a hot, juicy li'l snatch like mine in your face? And here I thought I was the pussy!"
		</p>
		<action name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA2" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="ChelIntroCaughtSubmitA2" name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA2" list="==>">
		<p>
			No longer able to take you fruitless efforts to satisfy her needs, the insane huntress rises off of you and jills herself off quickly, sinking her fingers into her sopping cunt, drawing sloppy, wet squelches and slurps as she finger fucks her slick delta inches away from your face.
		</p>
		<p>
			"Oooh fuck!~ Mmmm~, now this is how ya make a kitty purrrrr. See how hot 'n ready my pussy is? Wanna know something? I-I...I'm gonna... I need to~... cuuuum~!"
		</p>
		<action name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA3" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="ChelIntroCaughtSubmitA3" name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA3" list="==>">
		<p>
			Driving her fingers into her drooling fuckhole faster and faster, the cat woman throws her head back and cries out, spreading her moist lower lips and giving you quite the view, letting you feel the heat of her love canal upon your abused face before squirting a small stream of kitty cum all over you, adding the pi&#xE8;ce de r&#xE9;sistance as retribution to your pitiful efforts.
		</p>
		<p>
			The demented cheetah wobbles away with shaky legs and a lightheaded grin before calling back to you. "Yo, [b:g:jackass:cum slut:asshole]! If I were you I'd keep that look. It's an improvement and not many people get to wear one of Chelsie's original works of art around. Ta-ta for now, loser!"
		</p>
		<action name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA4" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="ChelIntroCaughtSubmitA4" name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA4" list="==>">
		<p>
			Now completely embarrassed, you wipe her feline honey from your face in shame and shuffle away before someone or something else takes advantage of you. Why was this Chelsie so hostile?
		</p>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			bottom.IncreaseSkill("cunnilingus");
		</script>
	</scene>

	<scene id="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitA" name="Chel_IntroCaughtSubmitCheck" list="==>">
		<filter target="bottom" type="skill" name="cunnilingus" value="0" />
		<p>
			Your assailant tumbles to the ground wildly as you smirk in satisfaction. Your weapon raised imposingly, you demand to know just what in god's name she was thinking. Looking up at you with wonder in her eyes, the mad woman grins from ear to ear and pounces, knocking you to the ground and locking her lips against yours.
		</p>
		<p>
			This is certainly a strange turn of events!
		</p>
	</scene>


</scenes>