<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE scenes [
	<!ELEMENT scenes (scene+)>
	<!ELEMENT scene (filter*,(p|script)*,action*)>
	<!ELEMENT filter EMPTY>
	<!ELEMENT script (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT action EMPTY>
	<!ATTLIST scene
		id ID #REQUIRED
		name CDATA #REQUIRED
		list CDATA #IMPLIED
		priority CDATA #IMPLIED
	>
	<!ATTLIST filter
		target (top|bottom) #REQUIRED
		type CDATA #REQUIRED
		name CDATA #IMPLIED
		value CDATA #IMPLIED
	>
	<!ATTLIST script type CDATA #FIXED "text/javascript">
	<!ATTLIST action name CDATA #REQUIRED>

	<!-- P can now have not only #PCDATA, but also IF and ELSE, in any combination. -->
	<!ELEMENT p (#PCDATA|if|else)*>
	<!ELEMENT if (#PCDATA|if|else)*>
	<!ELEMENT else (#PCDATA|if|else)*>
	<!-- Same as FILTER above. -->
	<!ATTLIST if
		target (top|bottom) #REQUIRED
		type CDATA #REQUIRED
		name CDATA #IMPLIED
		value CDATA #IMPLIED
	>
]>

<scenes>
	<!-- Written by PillowShout -->
	
	<!-- Player win rapes -->
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerWinImpRapeStart" name="(rape start)">
	<filter target="bottom" type="bodylev" name="imp" />
	<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="terms/generic" value="imp"/>
		<p>
			Seeing this as the perfect opportunity for some payback, you stand over the enfeebled [b:title] and smirk as [b:he] glares up at you. You hold [b:his] head between your <if target="top" type="has" name="quadruped">[t:feet]</if><else>hands</else>, force [b:him] to look you in the eyes and tell [b:him] in no uncertain terms that [b:he] is yours to do with as you please.
			
		</p>
		<p/>
		<p>
			The [b:title]'s eyes widen and [b:he] struggles for a moment before you subdue [b:him] again. Once you have a firm hold on [b:him], [b:he] finally seems to realize that [b:he]'s not going anywhere on [b:his] own and gives up fighting.
		</p>
		<action name="player win get generic blowjob" />
		<action name="player win generic get eaten out" />
		<action name="player win generic butt fuck" />
		<action name="player win generic vaginal ride" />
		<action name="player win generic anal ride" />
		<action name="leave the imp" />
	</scene>
	
	
	
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerWinLeave" name="leave the imp" list="Leave">
		<p>
			Although you find yourself enjoying the [b:title]'s submission, once you're given a moment to better examine [b:him], you realize that [t:he] has little to interest you with. You sigh disappointedly and release [b:his] head, leaving the [b:title] to stare at you in confusion as you walk away.
		</p>
	</scene>
	
	
	
	<!-- Player loss rapes -->
	
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpRapeStart" name="(loss rape start)">
		<filter target="top" type="bodylev" name="imp" />
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="terms/generic" value="imp"/>
		<p>
			After taking a final hit from the [t:title], you grunt in pain and fall to the ground beaten and exhausted. You try to push yourself up, but a sudden pressure on the top of your head forces you back onto the ground. 
		</p>
		<p/>
		<p>
			You look up and see the [t:title] holding you down, [t:his] dagger-like fangs showing in a predatory grin. <if target="top" type="isfather">
				Though as [t:he] gets a look at your face, [t:his] expression changes as he seems to recognise you. He looks down and notices the slight bulge in your stomach and his grin returns, though now there seems to be a hint of accomplishment in addition to the lust. 
			</if><else>
				<if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="carnality" value="33">
				Your heart drops as you quickly realize that you're not going to be leaving until this [t:title]'s had [t:his] way with you.</if><else>
				<if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="carnality" value="66">In return, you smile cautiously and feel your loins start to tingle as you realize what [t:he] intends to do with you.</if>
				<else>Your smile quickly joins [t:his] as you realize what [t:he] has in mind. This might not be the way you meant to go about it, but you're not about to turn down a free fuck.</else></else>
			</else>
		</p>
		<action name="player loss imp oral rape" />
		<action name="player loss imp anal rape" />
		<action name="player loss imp vaginal rape" />
	</scene>
	
	
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpOralRape" name="player loss imp oral rape">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<p>
			The [t:title] grabs you roughly by the back of the head and forces your face in front of [t:his] crotch. As [t:he] holds you there, [t:he] grunts and growls something that you can't understand while pointing first at [t:his] [cockrand] and then at you. At first you don't realize what [t:he] wants you to do, but as soon as [t:he] shoves your face into [t:his] groin, it immediately becomes very clear.
		</p>
		<p/>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
			
				var carn = bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value;
				if (carn < 33)
				{
					print("Disgusted by what [t:he] intends, you put your ");
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("[b:feet]")
					else
						print("hands");
						
					print(" on [t:his] hips and try to push yourself away. You barely manage to bring your face off of [t:his] [cockrand] before [t:he] suddenly jerks your head back and slaps you across the cheek. Shocked by the sudden impact, you barely react as [t:he] ");
					
					if(top.HasItemInSlot("hand"))
						print("pulls out [t:his] [t:equipment:hand] and points it at your neck.");
					else
						print("grabs you throat and viciously growls at you.");
						
					print("\n\nSeeing that you have no real options here, you decide that staying alive is more important than dignity and quickly nod. Pleased with your choice, the [t:title] smiles savagely and takes [t:his] ");
					
					if(top.HasItemInSlot("hand"))
						print("[t:equipment:hand]");
					else
						print("hand");
						
					print(" away from your neck before pushing your face in front of [t:his] [cockrand] and letting go of your head.");
				}
				else if (carn < 66)
				{
					print("Unsure of how he wants you proceed, you decide to start by rubbing your cheek against his [cockrand] and hope that it gets a reaction out of him. It seems to as he grunts approvingly, and soon after that, he lets go of your head. Now that you've got some room to move, you pull your face back and take a moment to get a better look at what you're dealing with.");
					print("\n\nIn front of you, the [t:title]'s [t:cocktype] [cockrand] hangs semi-erect between his legs, and seeing it so close makes you start to feel giddy at the prospect of tasting that thing. Not bothering to make this into anything more than it is, you quickly grab [t:his] [cockrand] with both ");
			
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("[b:feet]")
					else
						print("hands");
						
					print(" and slide your tongue along its underside as you take it into your mouth. ");
				}
				else
				{
					print("You inhale deeply and take in the scent of his musk before you slowly slide your tongue between your lips and " );
					
					if(bottom.GetToken("tongue").Text == "long")
						print("wrap as much of it as you can around his [cockrand].");
					else
						print("lick around the part of his shaft nearest to your mouth.");
		
					print(" Surprised by your enthusiasm, the [t:title] drops [t:his] hand from your head and staggers back a step.\n\nThis, however, does nothing to deter you, and you keep your face firmly planted between his thighs while slowly ");
					
					if(bottom.GetToken("tongue").Text == "long")
						print("stroking his shaft with your prehensile tongue.");
					else
						print("dragging your tongue along [t:his] [cockrand].");
					
		
					print(" [t:His] [cockrand] hardens quickly as you suck and lick at its length, and as soon as its hard enough to fuck, you slide your tongue up the side of [t:his] shaft and then wrap your lips around its tip before finally sliding it into your mouth.");
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="player loss imp skull fuck" />
		<action name="player loss imp willing blow" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpSkullFuck" name="player loss imp skull fuck">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="carnality" value="33"/>
		<p>
			You stare at [t:his] [t:cocktype] [cockrand] for a few seconds as it hangs between [t:his] legs before a sudden growl from the [t:title] spurs you into action. You grasp [t:his] [cockrand] with your both <if target="bottom" type="has" name="quadruped">[b:feet]</if><else>hands</else> and start to run them along its length. In no time at all, [t:his] [cockrand] has gone from hanging limply in front of [t:his] balls, to rock hard and jutting out from [t:his] crotch.
		</p>
		<p/>
		<p>
			As you continue to stroke [t:his] length, you begin to wonder if you can get away with just giving [t:him] a <if target="bottom" type="has" name="quadruped">[b:foot]</if><else>hand</else>job. However, your hopes are quickly dashed as the [t:title] pulls your <if target="bottom" type="has" name="quadruped">[b:feet]</if><else>hands</else> away from [t:his] [cockrand] and brings it closer to your face. You gulp as you realize that its do or die time, and you slowly open your mouth and take [t:his] cockhead inside.
		</p>
		<p/>
		<p>
			As the bottom of [t:his] [cockrand] brushes your tongue, you nearly choke as you're suddenly given a strong taste of not only the [t:title]'s potent musk, but most likely that of a recent victim's as well. You reluctantly start moving your head back and forth along first half of the [t:title]'s [cockrand] and fight the urge to gag as you slowly begin fellating him.
		</p>
		<action name="player loss imp skull fuck finish" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpSkullFuckFinish" name="player loss imp skull fuck finish">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="carnality" value="33"/>
		<p>
			You barely get more than a few seconds in to your blowjob before the [t:title] grows tired of your lackluster efforts and decides to take matters into [t:his] own hands by grabbing your head and ramming [t:his] [cockrand] down your throat.
		</p>
		<p/>
		<p>
			You choke and sputter as [t:he] draws back, but [t:he] gives you less than a second to recover before [t:he] shoves [t:his] [cockrand] down your throat again. As [t:he] starts pistoning into your mouth, you try futilely to force [t:his] hips away from your face. Unfortunately, you're still too weak to overpower the [t:title], and you give up on trying to push [t:him] away and focus entirely drawing breath between [t:his] thrusts.
		</p>
		<p/>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[

				print("Less than a minute goes by before you feel [t:his] thrusts getting shorter and faster, and even your oxygen starved mind realizes that [t:he]'s probably getting close to orgasm. A few seconds later you feel [t:him] stop and tense up before [t:his] oily [cumrand] starts shooting into the back of your mouth.\n\nYou nearly gag at the taste and fight the urge to retch");
					
				var cum = top.CumAmount();
				if(cum < 15)
					print(" as you feel the warm fluid pooling on the back of your tongue.");
				else if (cum < 40)
					print(" as the warm fluid fills the back of your mouth and starts leaking down your chin.");
				else
					print(", but as the warm fluid floods your mouth, you can't help but swallow some of it.");
				print(" Now that [t:he]'s had [t:his] fill, the [t:title] pulls his [cockrand] out of your mouth and leaves you to spit and cough as [t:he] settles down to rest.");
		
		
				top.Orgasm();
				bottom.ChangeStat("carnality", 1);
				bottom.IncreaseSkill("fellatio");
			]]>
		</script>
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpWillingBlow" name="player loss imp willing blow">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="value_gteq" name="carnality" value="33"/>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				var skill = bottom.GetSkillLevel("fellatio");
				
				if(skill < 1)
				{
					print("Now that you've got [t:his] [cockrand] in you mouth, you're not really sure about how to proceed. Deciding that a bit of experimentation is in order, you first try to take his [cockrand] as deep as it will go. Unfortunately, you happen to trigger your gag reflex and end up biting down on the [t:title]'s [cockrand]. [t:He] yelps in  pain and yanks his [cockrand] out of your mouth as you're left coughing and sputtering.\n\n");
					print("Clearly unimpressed with your lack of experience, the [t:title] decides that it would be better and safer to do things [t:him]self. As [t:he] steps towards you and brings his [cockrand] near your lips, you open you mouth to show [t:him] that you're ready to try again. You're caught completely by surprize then as he instead grabs you by the sides of your head and rams [t:his] [cockrand] down your throat.\n\n");
					print("You choke and gag as [t:he] suddenly draws back, but [t:he] gives you less than a second to recover before [t:he] shoves [t:his] [cockrand] down your throat again. You struggle to breath as the [t:title] starts pistoning into your mouth, and at first you try to push [t:him] away. Quickly though, you realize that [t:he] has no intention of stopping or letting you continue on your own, and so you focus on trying to find a way to safely draw breath while [t:he] skull fucks you.");
				}
				else if (skill < 3)
				{
					print("This isn't the first time you've had someone else's cock in your mouth, and by this point you're doubtful that it'll be the last. After a quick lick of the [t:title]'s [cockrand] as it sits in your mouth, you pull your head away from [t:his] crotch and reposition yourself so that you're seated more comfortably. The [t:title] continues to stand and wait patiently as you use your ");
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("[b:feet]");
					else
						print("hands");
					print(" to pull [t:his] [cockrand] into your mouth again.\n\n");
					print("Having learnt from experience, you wrap your lips around your teeth and then start slowly moving your head back and forth along [t:his] [cockrand]. Using your tongue, you lick along the bottom of [t:his] [cockrand] each time it enters your mouth, and every so often you suck on the head as it leaves. You continue like this for a while, but it's not long before you feel the [t:title] take hold of your head and start thrusting [t:him]self into your mouth a bit each time you push towards [t:his] groin.\n\n");
					print("Deciding that it's better to just go along with it, you keep moving [t:his] [cockrand] in and out of your mouth, even as [t:his] thrusts start to increase their pace and depth.");
				}
				else
				{
				print("With the [t:title]'s [cockrand] still nestled between your lips, you place a ");
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("[b:foot]");
					else
						print("hand");
					print(" softly on [t:his] stomach and push backwards while pulling down with your mouth. It takes [t:him] a moment to figure out what you want [t:him] to do, but eventually [t:he] sits down and lays on [t:his] back, all the while your mouth stays attached to [t:his] [cockrand]. Once [t:he]'s laying down, you look up at the [t:title] and smile around [t:his] [cockrand] before you get to work on giving [t:him] the blowjob of [t:his] life.\n\n");
					print("You start by slowly drawing your mouth off of [t:his] [cockrand] while grinding your [tonguetype] tongue into the underside of [t:his] shaft, and only stopping when you get to the tip. [t:His] [cockrand] twitches in your mouth as you start rolling your tongue around the underside of [t:his] cockhead, and in less than a few seconds you have [t:him] groaning and curling [t:his] toes as your tongue continues its assault on [t:his] [cockrand].\n\n");
					print("You stop abruptly when you feel the [t:title]'s hands on the back of your head, trying to force you down. Rather than fight [t:him], you quickly smile and wrap your lips around your teeth before you take the [t:title]'s [cockrand] down to the hilt.");
				}
				
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="player loss imp willing blow finish"/>
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpWillingBlowFinish" name="player loss imp willing blow finish">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="value_gteq" name="carnality" value="33"/>
		
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				var skill = bottom.GetSkillLevel("fellatio");
				
				if(skill < 1)
					print("Less than a minute goes by before you feel [t:his] thrusts getting shorter and faster, and even your oxygen starved mind realizes that [t:he]'s probably getting close to orgasm. You do what you can to help him along and try sucking each time [t:he] withdraws. This seems to do the trick as a few seconds later you feel [t:him] stop and tense up before [t:his] oily [cumrand] starts shooting into the back of your throat.");
				else if (skill < 3)
					print("It's not long before the [t:title] has speed up to the point that you can no longer keep up with [t:him], and you instead surrender yourself to waiting out the rest of the [t:title]'s face fucking. The [t:title] continues to drive [t:his] [t:cocktype] [cockrand] into your mouth as fast and hard as [t:he] can, but as seems to be the norm with [t:his] kind, [t:he]'s able to keep it up for less than a minute before you feel [t:his] body tense up and [t:his] oily [cumrand] start squirting into the back of your mouth.");
				else
				{
					print("The [t:title]'s hips thrust forward instinctively even though there's nowhere left to go, and you hold your breath as [t:his] hands hold your head tight against [t:his] groin. Still smiling, you hold your breath and once more start using your tongue to milk [t:his] [cockrand]. [t:His] grip on your head quickly weakens and you pull back before breathing deeply through your nose.\n\n");
					print("You decide that it's time to end this and start bobbing your head up and down in his lap while using your tongue to massage [t:his] [cockrand]. The [t:title], a testament to the staying power of [t:his] kind, lasts less than a minute before you feel [t:his] body tense up and [t:his] oily [cumrand] start squirting onto the back of your tongue.");
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		<p>
			You suck and swallow as the warm fluid squirts into your mouth, and you feel a lusty tingle in your gut as his [cumrand] settles there. The [t:title] groans as you continue to milk his [cockrand] with your tongue, but as soon as his [cumrand] stops flowing, [t:he] pushes your face off [t:his] [cockrand] and leaves you to catch your breath as [t:he] settles down to recover on [t:his] own.
		</p>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				top.Orgasm();
				bottom.ChangeStat("carnality", 1);
				bottom.IncreaseSkill("fellatio");
			]]>
		</script>
	</scene>
	
	
	
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpAnalRape" name="player loss imp anal rape">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		
		<p>
			The [t:title] forces your head to the ground and holds you there for a moment. [t:He] growls something unintelligible and after a final shove, removes [t:his] hand from your head. 
		</p>
		<p/>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				var carn = bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value;
				if (carn < 33)
				{
					print("You try to get up again, only to have [t:him] shove you back down, this time with ");
					
					if(top.HasItemInSlot("hand"))
						print("[t:his] [t:equipment:hand] pointed under your chin. ");
					else
						print("[t:his] other hand closed around your throat. ");
		
					print("Taking the hint, you resign yourself to whatever fate this [t:title] has in mind for you and wait anxiously as [t:he] takes [t:his] ");

					if(top.HasItemInSlot("hand"))
						print("[t:equipment:hand]");
					else
						print("hand");
						
					print(" away from your neck.\n\nYou follow him with your eyes as [t:he] walks around to your backside and shudder anxiously as you then feel [t:him] take hold of your [b:hips] and lift your ass into the air. ");
					
					if(bottom.HasVagina())
						print("A knot slowly forms in your stomach as you're forced to wait for [t:him] to make the next move.");
					else
						print("With only one hole back there, it doesn't take long for you to figure out what the [t:title] has in mind.");
				}
				else if (carn < 66)
				{
					print("You keep your head down and looking forward as you hear [t:him] walk around to your backside. Those lusty tingles from earlier work their way up to butterflies in your stomach as you wait to see what [t:he] does.\n\n");
					print("After a short while of not hearing anything from [t:him], you can't stand not knowing anymore and look over your shoulder. You see [t:him] eyeing your [b:ass] with ");
					
					var ass = bottom.Path("ass/size").Value;
					if(ass < 6)
						print ("a disappointed frown");
					else if(ass < 10)
						print("a contemplative frown");
					else if(ass < 16)
						print("a satisfied smile");
					else
						print("a gleeful grin");
						
					print(" on [t:his] face before [t:he] seems to decide that [t:he]'s seen enough and moves toward your rear. You continue to watch as [t:he] grabs you by your [b:hips] and lifts your ass into the air.");
				}
				else
				{
					print("You continue to grin salaciously, and in anticipation of the [t:title]'s desires, you lift your ass into the air and give it a good shake. The growling chuckle that comes from behind you gives you a little thrill as the [t:title] seems to enjoy the show.\n\n");
					print("You jump as you feel something hard strike your [b:ass] and look behind yourself to see the [t:title] holding [t:his] hand up momentarily before taking another swing. You shudder happily from the impact and rest your head on your ");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("[b:feet]");
					else
						print("hands");
		
					print(" as you wait to see what [t:he] does next.");
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		
		<action name="player loss imp anal rape 2" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpAnalRape2" name="player loss imp anal rape 2">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants") || bottom.HasItemInSlot("underpants"))
				{
					print("Now that [t:he]'s got you how [t:he] wants you, the [t:title] decides that it's time to get down to business and starts to remove your attire. Seeming to care little for what you're wearing, [t:he] ");
					if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants"))
					{
						var pants = bottom.GetEquippedItemBySlot("pants");
						var pronoun = "it";
						if(pants.HasToken("plural"))
							pronoun = "them";
						
						if(pants.CanReachThrough())
							print("hastily lifts up your [b:equipment:pants] and throws " + pronoun + " over your back");
						else if (pants.IsSuit())
							print("hastily takes your [b:equipment:pants] and tosses " + pronoun + " off to the side");
						else
							print("hastily pulls down your [b:equipment:pants] and leaves " + pronoun + " around your legs")
					}
					if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants") && bottom.HasItemInSlot("underpants"))
						print(" and then ");
					if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("underpants"))
					{
						var pronoun = "it";
						if(bottom.GetEquippedItemBySlot("underpants").HasToken("plural"))
							pronoun = "them";
					
						print("nearly rips your [b:equipment:underpants] as [t:he] pulls " + pronoun + " down off your ass");
					}
	
					print(".\n\n[t:He] seems to take a moment to enjoy the view of your now exposed rear before [t:he] steps forward and takes hold of your hips with one hand before using the other to line up [t:his] [cockrand] with your [b:anuslooseness] [anusrand].");
				}
				else
				{
					print("As the [t:title] stands behind you, [t:he] seems almost happy to find that you're not wearing anything bellow the waist, and gives you ");
					
					if(bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value < 66)
						print("a quick");
					else 
						print("another");
						
					print(" slap on the butt to show [t:his] appreciation. Using [t:his] hands, [t:he] spreads your ass cheeks apart and stares greedily at your [b:anuslooseness] [anusrand]. ");
					print("\n\nAfter a few seconds have passed, the [t:title] decides that [t:he]'s seen enough and drops one of [t:his] hands from your ass and instead uses it to line up the head of [t:his] [cockrand] with your [anusrand].");
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		
		<p>
			You feel the precum slicked head of the [t:title]'s [cockrand] press into your [anusrand], <if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="carnality" value="33">
				and you instinctively pull away and clench your sphincter. Not having any of that, [t:he] grabs you by the hips and pulls you back into place.
			</if><else>
				and you relax as much as you can and push back. [t:He] grunts approvingly as [t:his] length slips off your [anusrand] and slides between your asscheeks.
			</else>
		</p>
		<p/>
		<p>
			<if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="ass/looseness" value="2">
				Once again, the [t:title] lines up [t:his] [cockrand] against your backdoor and pushes forward. Your [b:anuslooseness] [anusrand] refuses to yeild, and you feel a sharp pain shoot up your spine as the [t:title] continues to push forward. You grunt and groan as [t:he] slowly forces [t:his] way in, until suddenly you yelp in pain as [t:he] finally manages to slip through.
			</if><else><if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="ass/looseness" value="4">
				The [t:title] once again lines up [t:his] [cockrand] against your backdoor and pushes forward. Your [b:anuslooseness] [anusrand] provides some brief resistance against [t:his] [cockrand], but after causing you only some minor discomfort, [t:he]'s managed stretch out your [anusrand] enough that it comfortably accommodates [t:him].
				</if><else>
					As [t:he] once again lines up [t:his] [cockrand] against your backdoor and pushes forward, your [b:anuslooseness] [anusrand] quickly gives in and swallows the [t:title]'s [cockrand] to the hilt. [t:He] seems surprized and a little disappointed that it went in so easily, but that doesn't stop [t:him] as [t:he] draws [t:his] [cockrand] back out before thrusting in once more.
				</else>
			</else>
		</p>
		<action name="player loss imp anal rape finish" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpAnalRapeFinish" name="player loss imp anal rape finish">
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[				
				var wasVirgin = bottom.RemoveVirgin(bottom.GetToken("ass"));
				var stretched = bottom.StretchHole(bottom.GetToken("ass"), top.GetToken("penis"))
				
				if(wasVirgin)
					print("Your eyes water as [t:he] pushes in again, your formerly virgin [anusrand] now painfully stretched around the [t:title]'s [cockrand]. [t:He]'s clearly not bothered by the amount of pain you're in as [t:he] continues to increase the force and speed of [t:his] thrusts. If anything, the [t:title] actually seems to be enjoying your discomfort.");
				else if (stretched)
					print("Even though this isn't the first time you've been taken in the ass, the [t:title]'s [cockrand] still leaves your [anusrand] painfully stretched, and you wouldn't be surprized to find yourself being a bit looser back there the next time you check. The [t:title] is clearly not bothered by the amount of pain you're in as [t:he] continues to increase the force and speed of [t:his] thrusts. If anything, [t:he] actually seems to be enjoying your discomfort."); 
				else if (bottom.Path("ass/looseness").Value < 4)
					print("As the [t:title] continues to thrust [t:his] [cockrand] in and out of your [anusrand], [t:he] slowly seems to be gaining momentum as the stream of precum leaking from [t:his] member serves to further lubricate your back passage. In little time at all, you're being repeatedly bumped forward by the [t:title]'s thrusts as [t:he] seems to have found [t:his] stride.");
				else
				{
					if(bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value < 33)
						print("As the [t:title] continues to pump into your [anusrand], it quickly becomes apparent that [t:his] member is much smaller than what you've dealt with in the past. You smile weakly at the [t:title]'s growing frustration, and you do everything in your power to make this as unsatisfying as possible for [t:him]. ");
					else
						print("Much to both your and the [t:title]'s growing disappointment, it's become very apparent that [t:his] member is much smaller than what you're [anusrand] is used to dealing with. Even with you clamping down as much as you can, the [t:title] soon grows tired of dealing with your [b:anuslooseness] [anusrand]. ");
						
					print("After stopping briefly, the [t:title] grabs your buttocks and squeezes them together around [t:his] [cockrand] and then starts pumping into you harder and faster than ever before.");
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		
		<p>
			The rhythmic slapping of the [t:title]'s hips against your backside slowly increases in tempo as [t:he] nears [t:his] climax. <if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="carnality" value="33">
				Wanting this ordeal to finally be over, you hold your face in your <if target="bottom" type="has" name="quadruped">[b:feet]</if><else>hands</else> and wait silently as [t:he] continues to hump away at your ass. You wince as the [t:title] suddenly digs [t:his] fingers into your <if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="ass/looseness" value="4">hips</if><else>ass cheeks</else> and thrusts in one final time. You're left feeling almost ill as [t:his] oily [cumrand] starts squirting into your rear.
			</if><else><if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="carnality" value="66">
					You moan contentedly and rest your face on your <if target="bottom" type="has" name="quadruped">[b:feet]</if><else>hands</else> as [t:he] continues to hump away at your ass. You jerk in surprize as the [t:title] suddenly digs [t:his] fingers into your <if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="ass/looseness" value="4">hips</if><else>ass cheeks</else>, and after [t:he] thrusts in one final time, you feel [t:his] pleasantly warm and oily [cumrand] start squirting into your backside.
				</if><else>
					You try to meet [t:him] stoke for stroke, but in your weakened state the most you can do is push back a little each time. You arch your back suddenly as the [t:title] digs [t:his] fingers into your <if target="bottom" type="value_lower" name="ass/looseness" value="4">hips</if><else>ass cheeks</else> and makes a final thrust, and immediately you feel [t:his] deliciously warm and oily [cumrand] start squirting into your back door.
				</else>
			</else>
		</p>
		<p/>
		<p>
			The [t:title] stays where [t:he] is for a while as [t:he] rides out [t:his] orgasm, and you quickly feel the volume of [t:his] ejaculations taper off to nothing. You're left waiting a moment more before you feel a sudden vacancy in your rectum and hear the wet sucking noise [t:his] [cockrand] makes as [t:he] pulls it out of your [anusrand]. You sigh in relief and slump down on the ground just before [t:title] decides to give you a parting smack on the ass.
		</p>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				top.Orgasm();
				
				bottom.ChangeStat("carnality", 1);	// From the Imp's cum
			]]>
		</script>
	</scene>
	
	
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpVaginalRape" name="player loss imp vaginal rape">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="vagina" />
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				var carn = bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value;
				
				print("The [t:title] lets go of your head and shoves you onto your back. ");
				
				if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants") || bottom.HasItemInSlot("underpants"))
				{
					print("You look down and see [t:him] staring intently at your ");
					
					if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants"))
						print("[b:equipment:pants:color]");
					else
						print("[b:equipment:underpants:color]");
						
					print(", and [t:his] [t:tonguetype] tongue slides between [t:his] lips as [t:he] undresses you with [t:his] eyes.\n\n");
					
					if(carn < 33)
					{
						print("The [t:title] quickly looses interest with just imaging what you've got and grabs onto your ");
						
						var pronoun = "it";
						var reach = false;
						if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants"))
						{
							print("[b:equipment:pants]");
							if(bottom.GetEquippedItemBySlot("pants").HasToken("plural"))
								pronoun = "them"
								
							reach = bottom.GetEquippedItemBySlot("pants").CanReachThrough();
						}
						else
						{
							print("[b:equipment:underpants]");
							if(bottom.GetEquippedItemBySlot("underpants").HasToken("plural"))
								pronoun = "them"
								
							reach = bottom.GetEquippedItemBySlot("underpants").CanReachThrough();
						}
							
						print(". Before [t:he] can remove " + pronoun + ", you grab hold of [t:his] arms and fight the [t:title] as [t:he] tries to ");
						
						if(reach)
							print("lift " + pronoun + " up.");
						else
							print("pull " + pronoun + " down."); 
				
						print("\n\nThe [t:title] apparently doesn't feel like dealing with this and wrestles out of your grip before [t:he] punches you in the stomach hard enough that it leaves you winded. You gasp and hold your sides as you fight for air while the [t:title] is left to remove your ");
						
						if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants"))
							print("[b:equipment:pants]");
						else
							print("[b:equipment:underpants]");
							
						print(" unhindered.\n\n");
					}
					else
					{
						print("Rather than leave [t:him] to imagine what you've got under your clothes, you decide to show [t:him] by ");
						
						if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants"))
						{
							var pants = bottom.GetEquippedItemBySlot("pants");
							
							if(pants.CanReachThrough())
								print("pulling up your [b:equipment:pants]");
							else
								print("slipping off your [b:equipment:pants]")
						}
						if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("pants") && bottom.HasItemInSlot("underpants"))
							print(" and ");
						if(bottom.HasItemInSlot("underpants"))			
							print("sliding your [b:equipment:underpants] down");
				
						print(". [t:He] seems to enjoy your willingness, and you decide to urge [t:him] on by ");
			
						if(bottom.HasToken("legs"))
							print("spreading your legs a bit wider");
						else
							print("rolling your hips forward");
							
						print(" and using your ");
						
						if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
							print("[b:feet]");
						else
							print("fingers");
						
						print(" to expose the pink interior of your [pussyrand].\n\n");
					}
					
					if(bottom.HasPenis())
						print("Although the [t:title] seems less than impressed with the [cocktype] [cockrand] [t:he] sees resting above your [pussyrand], [t:he] apparently decides that it's not important and");
					else
						print("[t:He] appears to pleased with what [t:he] finds beneath your clothes and");
						
					if(bottom.HasToken("legs"))
						print(", after a moment of deliberation, rolls you onto your stomach and lifts your ass up in the air.")
					else
					{
						print(" seats [t:him]self on your hips so that [t:his] [cockrand] rests just bellow your ")
						
						if(bottom.HasToken("slimeblob"))
							print("gooey [pussyrand].");
						else
							print("slit.");
					}
				}
				else
				{
					print("You look down to see [t:him] staring excitedly at your exposed groin, and as you think back on the fight, you remember [t:him] doing the same thing then. ");
					
					if(carn < 33)
						print("Your cheeks flush in embarrassment, and you wonder if once you get out of here, you should try to find something to cover up with.");
					else if(carn < 66)
						print("You crack an amused smile and consider the possibility that some of your recent victories may have come from fighting distracted opponents rather than pure skill.");
					else
					{
						print("You grin lustfully and ");
						if(bottom.HasToken("legs"))
							print("spread your legs a bit wider");
						else
							print("roll your hips forward");
						print(" to give [t:him] a better view, now that [t:he] has the opportunity to enjoy it.");
					}
					
					print("\n\nThe [t:title] smiles salaciously as [t:he] ");
					if(bottom.HasPenis())
						print("catches sight of the [pussyrand] you have hidden bellow your [cockrand]");
					else
						print("looks over your exposed [pussyrand]");
					
					print(", and [t:he] growls out something that you can't make sense of while ");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("legs"))
					{
						if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped") || bottom.HasToken("taur"))
							print("slipping [t:his] hand between your hind legs.");
						else
							print("slipping [t:his] hand between your thighs.");
					}
					else if (bottom.HasToken("snaketail"))
						print("running [t:his] hand over your slit.");
					else if (bottom.HasToken("slimeblob"))
						print("shoving [t:his] hand into your gooey crotch.");
					else
						print("grabbing your exposed crotch with [t:his] hand.");
						
					if(carn < 33)
					{
						print("\n\nYou quickly ");
						
						if(bottom.HasToken("legs"))
							print("clamp your legs")
						else if (bottom.HasToken("snaketail"))
							print("coil your tail");
						else if (bottom.HasToken("slimeblob"))
							print("wrap the gel near your groin");			
				
						print(" around the [t:title]'s hand and try to pull [t:his] arm away from your crotch with your ");
						
						if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
							print("[b:feet].");
						else
							print("hands.");
						
						print(" The [t:title] growls in frustration and grabs your ");
						
						if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
							print("fore legs");
						else
							print("arms");

							print(" with [t:his] other hand and holds them down on the ground as [t:he] continues to explore your [pussyrand].");
					}
					else
					{
						if(bottom.HasToken("legs")) 
							print("\n\nYou spread your legs wider still");
						else
							print("\n\nYou roll your hips back a bit");
							
						print(" and hum pleasantly as [t:he] explores your [pussyrand] with [t:his] fingers. Your hips buck forward as [t:he] slips a finger into you and you hear a growling laugh come from the [t:title] as [t:he] continues to finger you.");
					}
					
					print("\n\nOnce [t:he]'s satisfied with what [t:he]'s found, the [t:title] pulls [t:his] hand out of your crotch and");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("legs"))
						print(", after a moment of deliberation, rolls you onto your stomach and lifts your ass in the air.");
					else
					{
						print(" seats [t:him]self on your hips so that [t:his] [cockrand] rests just bellow your ");
						
						if(bottom.HasToken("slimeblob"))
							print("gooey [pussyrand].");
						else
							print("slit.");
					}
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="player loss imp vaginal rape with legs" />
		<action name="player loss imp vaginal rape no legs" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpVaginalRapeWithLegs" name="player loss imp vaginal rape with legs">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="vagina" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="legs"/>
		
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				var carn = bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value;
				
				print("As you peek over your shoulder, you see the [t:title] looking over your backside with lascivious greed while [t:his] hand slowly strokes [t:his] growing erection. ");
				
				if(carn < 33)
				{
					print("Your cheeks flush in shame and ");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("tail"))
						print("your [tailtype] tail clamps down between your legs");
					else
						print("you squeeze your legs together");
						
					print(" as the [t:title] continues to stare at your rear. Clearly displeased with your modesty, [t:he] swats you hard on the rump and ");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("tail"))
						print("pulls your tail up and out of the way.");
					else
						print("shoves [t:his] hands in between your thighs and pulls them apart.");
				}
				else
				{
					print("A smile cracks on your face, and you ");
					if(bottom.HasToken("tail"))
						print("lift your [tailtype] tail out of the way");
					else
						print("move your legs apart and push out your ass");
					print(" to give [t:him] unobstructed access to your rear. The [t:title] grunts in appreciation and you notice [t:his] eyes now seem to be fixed on your [pussyrand].");
				}
				
				print("\n\nThe [t:title] then grabs on to your hips and you feel the precum slicked head of [t:his] [cockrand] poking at the entrance to your [pussyrand]. ")
				
				if(carn < 33)
					print("You try to pull forward and struggle out of the [t:title]'s grip, but [t:he] doesn't let you get far before [t:he] roughly grabs you by the hips and pulls you back into place. Once again, you feel [t:him] taking position and prodding [t:his] cock head at the opening of your [pussyrand].");
				else
					print("A happy moan escapes you as you push back into [t:him], and your hips jerk as [t:his] [cockrand] slides between your labia and over your [clitrand]. You hear the [t:title] groan appreciatively as [t:he] pulls his [cockrand] back up to your entrance.");

				var stretched = bottom.StretchHole(bottom.GetToken("vagina"), top.GetToken("penis"))
				
				print("\n\n");
					
				if(bottom.GetToken("vagina").HasToken("virgin"))
					print("The [t:title] pushes forward, and [t:he] barely makes it in before you feel [t:his] [cockrand] push up against something in your [pussyrand]. You hear [t:his] growling laughter come from behind you before [t:he] suddenly pushes forward, hard, and you feel something pop. You moan pitifully as a deep pain pours from your newly bloodied [pussyrand], which then doubles in intensity as the [t:title] pulls back and thrusts in again, just as abruptly.");
				else if(stretched)
					print("As the [t:title] pushes forward, you feel the walls of your [pussyrand] stretch uncomfortably around [t:his] [cockrand], and you get the feeling that you're going to be a little looser down there once this is done. You hear a satisfied groan come from behind you as [t:he] continues to push forward until, finally, you feel [t:his] hips press briefly against your ass as [t:he] bottoms out and then draws back for another thrust.");
				else
				{
					print("The [t:title] enters your [pussyrand] easily")
					if(carn < 33)
						print(" even though you can feel yourself clench up as [t:he] does so.");
					else
						print(", and you moan contentedly as [t:his] [cockrand] fills you.");
						
					print(" Seeming to want to draw this out a bit, the [t:title] slowly drags [t:his] [cockrand] out of your [pussyrand] before pushing it back in with the same agonizing slowness. ");
	
					if(carn < 33)
					{
						print("You hide your face in your ");
						
						if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
							print("[b:feet]");
						else
							print("hands");
		
						print(" as your loins slowly betray you and start to grow warmer and wetter from [t:his] teasing thrusts.");
					}
					else
						print("Eager to speed this up, you rock forward and backward with each of [t:his] trusts and slowly force [t:him] to increase [t:his] tempo.");
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="player loss imp vaginal rape with legs finish" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpVaginalRapeWithLegsFinish" name="player loss imp vaginal rape with legs finish">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="vagina" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="legs"/>
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				
				var wasVirgin = bottom.RemoveVirgin(bottom.GetToken("vagina"));
				var carn = bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value;
				
				if(wasVirgin)
					print("The sharp pain in your loins slowly dulls as [t:he] continues the thrust [t:his] [cockrand] into your abused [pussyrand]. "); 
				else
					print("[t:He] eventually ceases [t:his] slow exploration of your [pussyrand], and starts thrusting into you more vigorously. ");
				
				print("The [t:title] doesn't take long to near [t:his] climax, and you ");
				
				if(wasVirgin || carn < 33)
					print("grimace");
				else
					print("moan happily");
				
				print(" as you feel [t:his] thrusts shorten and speed up. Barely half a minute passes before you feel [t:his] [cockrand] grow rock hard, and after on one final thrust, [t:his] oily and ")
					
				if(carn < 33)
					print("uncomfortably");
				else
					print("pleasantly");

				print(" warm [cumrand] starts squirting into your [pussyrand].");
				
				print("\n\n[t:He] stands there for a moment with his hips pressed hard up against your back side, and only after you feel the jets of [cumrand] trickle down to nothing does [t:he] finally pull out.\n\n");
				
				if (wasVirgin)
				{
					print("As the [t:title] recovers on [t:his] own, you're left to tend to your raw [pussyrand]. You slowly reach a ");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("[b:foot]");
					else
						print("hand");
						
					print(" down to your swollen labia and feel around. While your lips feel a bit tender, you don't actually feel any pain until you run ");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("your [b:foot]");
					else
						print("a finger");
						
					print(" over your entrance. You choose to take solace in that fact that this isn't the worst pain you've ever felt, but all the same, your [pussyrand] is undoubtably going to be sore for a while.");
				}
				else
				{
					if(carn < 33)
						print("You sigh in relief as the [t:title] finally leaves you to yourself, and your first thought is to sit up and drain as much of [t:his] [cumrand] from your [pussyrand] as possible. In sort order you feel the slimy mess trickling down your leg, and after it stops flowing, all you're left with is the hope that it didn't take.");
					else
						print("You lay with your chest against the ground for a moment as you enjoy the lingering feeling of fullness that the [t:title]'s [cumrand] provides. Sadly, it can't last forever, and you sit up and wait to clean up the inevitable deluge of [cumrand] from your [pussyrand].");
				}
				
				top.Orgasm();
				
				bottom.Fertilize(top);
				bottom.ChangeStat("carnality", 1);	// From the Imp's cum
			]]>
		</script>
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpVaginalRapeNoLegs" name="player loss imp vaginal rape no legs">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="vagina" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="hasnot" name="legs"/>
		
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				var carn = bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value;
				
				print("You feel the [t:title] adjusting [t:his] position on your lap, and as you try to sit up and see what [t:he]'s doing, [t:he] shoves his hand under your neck and forces your head back to the ground. ");
				
				if(carn < 33)
				{
					print("Immediately, you wrap your hands around the [t:title]'s arm and try to pull [t:him] off, but [t:he] only tightens t[t:his] grip on your throat and growls threateningly at you. Despite pushing as hard as you can, you realize that you ultimately can't win and let go of [t:his] arm.");
				}
				else
				{
					print("Although initially surprized by [t:his] sudden action, you quickly relax and lay your head back while [t:he] continues to line up his [cockrand] with your [pussyrand]. Content with your submission, the [t:title] relaxes [t:his] grip on your neck.");
				}
				
				print("\n\nThe [t:title] then slides his hips forward and you feel the precum slicked head of [t:his] [cockrand] poking at the entrance to your [pussyrand]. ")
				
				if(carn < 33)
					print("You shut your eyes and try roll your hips to the side to force [t:his] [cockrand] away from your [pussyrand], but any thoughts of last resistance leave you as [t:he] growls again and forcefully tightens [t:his] grip on your throat.");
				else
					print("A happy moan escapes you as you roll your hips forward and [t:his] [cockrand] slides between your labia and over your [clitrand]. You hear the [t:title] growl appreciatively before [t:he] pulls his [cockrand] back up to your entrance.");

				var stretched = bottom.StretchHole(bottom.GetToken("vagina"), top.GetToken("penis"))
				
				print("\n\n");
					
				if(bottom.GetToken("vagina").HasToken("virgin"))
					print("The [t:title] pushes forward, and [t:he] barely makes it in before you feel [t:his] [cockrand] push up against something in your [pussyrand]. You see [t:him] grin with pedatory delight before [t:he] suddenly pushes forward, hard, and you feel something pop. You moan pitifully as a deep pain pours from your newly bloodied [pussyrand], which then doubles in intensity as the [t:title] pulls back and thrusts in again, just as abruptly.");
				else if(stretched)
					print("As the [t:title] pushes forward, you feel the walls of your [pussyrand] stretch uncomfortably around [t:his] [cockrand], and you get the feeling that you're going to be a little looser down there once this is done. You hear a satisfied groan come from behind you as [t:he] continues to push forward until, finally, you feel [t:his] hips press briefly against yours as [t:he] bottoms out and then draws back for another thrust.");
				else
				{
					print("The [t:title] enters your [pussyrand] easily")
					if(carn < 33)
						print(" even though you can feel yourself clench up as [t:he] does so.");
					else
						print(", and you moan contentedly as [t:his] [cockrand] fills you.");
						
					print(" Seeming to want to draw this out a bit, the [t:title] slowly drags [t:his] [cockrand] out of your [pussyrand] before pushing it back in with the same agonizing slowness. ");
	
					if(carn < 33)
					{
						print("You close your eyes and bite your knuckle as your loins slowly betray you and start to grow warmer and wetter from [t:his] teasing thrusts.");
					}
					else
						print("Eager to speed this up, you push up your hips with each of [t:his] trusts and slowly force [t:him] to increase [t:his] tempo.");
				}
			]]>
		</script>
		<action name="player loss imp vaginal rape no legs finish" />
	</scene>
	<scene id="Pillow_PlayerLossImpVaginalRapeNoLegsFinish" name="player loss imp vaginal rape no legs finish">
		<filter target="top" type="has" name="penis" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="has" name="vagina" />
		<filter target="bottom" type="hasnot" name="legs"/>
		
		<script type="text/javascript">
			<![CDATA[
				
				var wasVirgin = bottom.RemoveVirgin(bottom.GetToken("vagina"));
				var carn = bottom.GetToken("carnality").Value;
				
				if(wasVirgin)
					print("The sharp pain in your loins slowly dulls as [t:he] continues the thrust [t:his] [cockrand] into your abused [pussyrand]. "); 
				else
					print("[t:He] eventually ceases [t:his] slow exploration of your [pussyrand], and starts thrusting into you more vigorously. ");
				
				print("The [t:title] doesn't take long to near [t:his] climax, and you ");
				
				if(wasVirgin || carn < 33)
					print("grimace");
				else
					print("moan happily");
				
				print(" as you feel [t:his] thrusts shorten and speed up. Barely half a minute passes before you feel [t:his] [cockrand] suddenly grow rock hard, and after on one final thrust, [t:his] oily and ")
					
				if(carn < 33)
					print("uncomfortably");
				else
					print("pleasantly");

				print(" warm [cumrand] starts squirting into your [pussyrand].");
				
				print("\n\n[t:He] sits there for a moment with his hips pressed hard up against yours, and only after you feel the jets of [cumrand] trickle down to nothing does [t:he] finally pull out.\n\n");
				
				if (wasVirgin)
				{
					print("As the [t:title] recovers on [t:his] own, you're left to tend to your raw [pussyrand]. You slowly reach a ");
					
					if(bottom.HasToken("quadruped"))
						print("[b:foot]");
					else
						print("hand");
						
					print(" down to your swollen labia and feel around. While your lips feel a bit tender, you don't actually feel any pain until you run a finger over your entrance. ");
					print("You choose to take solace in that fact that this isn't the worst pain you've ever felt, but all the same, your [pussyrand] is undoubtably going to be sore for a while.");
				}
				else
				{
					if(carn < 33)
					{
						print("You sigh in relief as the [t:title] finally leaves you to yourself, and your first thought is to sit up and drain as much of [t:his] [cumrand] from your [pussyrand] as possible. In sort order you feel the slimy mess trickling down the front of your ");
						if(bottom.HasToken("snaketail"))
							print("tail");
						else
							print("lower body")
						print(", and after it stops flowing, all you're left with is the hope that it didn't take.");
						
					}
					else
						print("You continue lay on the ground for a while as you enjoy the lingering feeling of fullness that the [t:title]'s [cumrand] provides. Sadly, it can't last forever, and you sit up and wait to clean up the inevitable deluge of [cumrand] from your [pussyrand].");
				}
				
				top.Orgasm();
				
				bottom.Fertilize(top);
				bottom.ChangeStat("carnality", 1);	// From the Imp's cum
			]]>
		</script>
	</scene>

</scenes>